Politician,Quote,Image URL,char_count,word_count,word_length,adv_count,adj_count,noun_count,verb_count,det_count,sentiment,named_entities,named_entities_count
Melissa Agard,potato chips  kitkat bars and viagra are not taxed in wisconsin because they are considered  essential,true,102,16,5.3125,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'GPE')",1
Melissa Agard,since       the state senate has only rejected five executive appointments  the gop today is more than doubling that number,true,123,19,5.157894736842105,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.4588,"('the state senate', 'ORG'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('gop', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE')",4
Instagram posts,lego donates model mri kits to hospitals to help children understand the procedure and reduce their anxiety,true,107,17,5.352941176470588,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.25,,0
Brian Krassenstein,it has been u s  policy  for at least    years  to require americans who intend to be evacuated from overseas to sign a promissory note,true,135,25,4.2,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.2263,"('at least    years', 'DATE'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2
Mike Oliverio,a few years back   mitchell stadium in bluefield  w va    was voted the best high school football field in america,true,114,20,4.45,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.6369,"('a few years', 'DATE'), ('america', 'GPE')",2
Instagram posts,beyonce paid     k for maryland metro to run later following weather delays for her concert,true,91,15,4.866666666666666,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('maryland', 'GPE')",1
Instagram posts,an    year old boy saved the lives of two people on the same day,true,64,14,3.4285714285714284,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.4215,"('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('the same day', 'DATE')",2
Kelda Helen Roys,infertility is treated differently than other issues and  often excluded from insurance coverage,true,96,13,6.384615384615385,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.34,,0
Francis Suarez,just last year   miami dade public schools  had over        new children         of which came from four countries of cuba  nicaragua  venezuela and haiti,true,154,23,4.869565217391305,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,"('just last year', 'DATE'), ('miami dade', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('cuba', 'GPE'), ('nicaragua', 'GPE'), ('venezuela', 'GPE'), ('haiti', 'GPE')",7
Tim Scott,for african american families in particular  the homeownership rate remains relatively unchanged since       the year the fair housing act was signed into law,true,158,23,5.608695652173913,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.3182,"('african american', 'NORP'), ('the year', 'DATE')",2
Robin Vos,when a basketball player or football or baseball player from another team plays in wisconsin  that one game s salary  they pay wisconsin income tax on it      so  if for some reason we do not have the brewers in wisconsin all of those player salaries that generate dollars for the state of wisconsin go away,true,307,55,4.454545454545454,37.0,37.0,37.0,37.0,37.0,0.1531,"('wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('wisconsin', 'GPE')",4
Facebook posts,if you need girl scout cookies this year and don t have a local troop to support  please consider buying from troop       which is entirely made up of girls living in nyc s homeless shelters,true,190,35,4.257142857142857,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,0.6124,"('this year', 'DATE'), ('don', 'PERSON')",2
Jonathan Martin,joe biden was older on his first day as president than ronald reagan was on his last day,true,88,18,3.9444444444444446,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('joe biden', 'PERSON'), ('ronald reagan', 'PERSON'), ('last day', 'DATE')",3
Kirsten Gillibrand,many law enforcement agencies didn t submit their  hate crime  data to the fbi,true,78,14,4.5,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.802,"('fbi', 'ORG')",1
Paul Ryan,wow county swing suburban voters  in wisconsin  don t vote for donald trump,true,75,13,4.6923076923076925,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.5859,"('wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('donald trump', 'PERSON')",2
Ron DeSantis,manhattan district attorney alvin bragg  has downgraded over     of the felonies to misdemeanors,true,96,13,6.076923076923077,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.5423,"('manhattan', 'GPE'), ('alvin bragg  ', 'PERSON')",2
Fentrice Driskell,of every     ron desantis  spends comes from the federal government,true,67,10,5.3,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('ron desantis', 'PERSON')",1
Robert Ortt,if new york s proposed limits on natural gas in buildings take effect  the grid today can t handle the increased electric load,true,126,23,4.478260869565218,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.5574,"('new york', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')",2
Tony Evers,wisconsin is the nation s top cranberry producer   in fact  our farmers harvest around    percent of the country s crop,true,119,20,4.7,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.2023,"('wisconsin', 'ORG')",1
Morgan Luttrell,biden drained america s strategic petroleum reserves to the lowest level since,true,78,12,5.583333333333333,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.6249,"('biden drained america', 'ORG')",1
Melissa Agard,historically  our spring elections  including for state supreme court  have a smaller turnout associated with them,true,114,16,6.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.5574,"('supreme court', 'ORG')",1
Tammy Baldwin,latina workers make    cents for every dollar earned by white  non hispanic men,true,79,13,4.846153846153846,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('latina workers make', 'PERSON'), ('hispanic', 'NORP')",2
Kevin Brady,joe biden s     billion for a union pension fund is  the largest private pension bailout in american history,true,108,18,4.777777777777778,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.1027,"('joe biden s', 'PERSON'), ('american', 'NORP')",2
Elise Stefanik,proposed rule would limit milk for wic participants,true,51,8,5.5,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,,0
Bryan Steil,in milwaukee   the  homicide  rate has nearly doubled in the past two years,true,75,13,4.538461538461538,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('milwaukee', 'GPE'), ('the past two years', 'DATE')",2
Joe Biden,gas prices are down back to where they were before russia invaded ukraine,true,73,13,4.6923076923076925,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('russia', 'GPE')",1
Joe Manchin,west virginia is poised to  receive    m for     orphaned well clean up projects across the state,true,97,16,4.625,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.7003,"('west virginia', 'GPE')",1
Everytown for Gun Safety,kari lake is opposed to red flag laws,true,37,8,3.75,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('kari lake', 'PERSON')",1
Lorraine Lewandrowski,it s not currently  legal for a new york state student to have a glass of fresh whole milk,true,90,19,3.736842105263158,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.2335,"('new york', 'GPE')",1
Tim Kaine,new haven  conn   had to issue bonds for a bridge after using funds for that bridge to pay for a police misconduct settlement,true,125,23,4.3478260869565215,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.1027,"('conn   ', 'GPE')",1
Wisconsin Republican Legislative leaders,wisconsin s         budget produced the first positive general fund balance since       and the governor s proposed         budget would return it to a deficit,true,159,23,5.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.2263,"('wisconsin s         ', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')",2
Robert Martwick,opposition to having a fully elected chicago board of education is in the  super minority,true,89,15,4.933333333333334,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.5994,"('chicago', 'GPE')",1
Greg Abbott,we now have more job openings than we do people who are on unemployment  we have     more job openings today than we did the month before the pandemic hit the state of texas,true,173,33,4.121212121212121,23.0,23.0,23.0,23.0,23.0,-0.4404,"('today', 'DATE'), ('the month', 'DATE'), ('texas', 'GPE')",3
Jeff Jackson,says he was  one of the    state senators  who voted against  north carolina s body camera law,true,94,17,4.235294117647059,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('north carolina', 'GPE')",2
Kevin Kiley,san francisco had twice as many drug overdose deaths as covid deaths last year,true,78,14,4.642857142857143,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('san francisco', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')",2
Kirk Cox,on virginia s new marijuana law   you can have up to one pound with only a     fine,true,83,17,3.588235294117647,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.2023,"('virginia', 'GPE'), ('marijuana', 'PERSON')",2
Van Wanggaard,foxconn  is the largest taxpayer in racine county,true,49,8,5.125,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('foxconn', 'GPE')",1
Zach Wahls,the federal american rescue plan will purchase more food from farmers for distribution,true,86,13,5.6923076923076925,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.5106,"('american', 'NORP')",1
Pete Buttigieg,there is racism physically built into some of our highways,true,58,10,4.9,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.6249,,0
Jim Justice,west virginia  is the only state to decline in population over the last    years,true,80,14,4.5,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('west virginia', 'GPE'), ('the last    years', 'DATE')",2
Terry McAuliffe,if you look at the average teacher pay compared to the average pay of your citizens  virginia ranks last,true,104,19,4.473684210526316,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.2023,"('virginia', 'GPE')",1
Barbara Dittrich,pot today is not the weed baby boomers were smoking,true,51,10,4.2,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('today', 'DATE')",1
Beth Wessel-Kroeschell,of americans and     of gun owners support requiring all gun buyers to pass a background check,true,94,16,4.6875,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.2732,"('americans', 'NORP')",1
Facebook posts,the georgia house passed a bill that  makes it a misdemeanor to give food or water to voters waiting in line,true,108,21,4.142857142857143,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,"('the georgia house', 'ORG')",1
Chuck Todd,the filibuster was never an idea of the founding fathers,true,56,10,4.7,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,,0
Energy Transfer,pipelines do not freeze  they are naturally insulated  they re buried beneath the ground,true,88,14,5.214285714285714,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.0382,,0
Chris Kapenga,the national academy of medicine points to a significant correlation between marijuana and psychosis  schizophrenia  and other psychotic disorders  particularly in teenagers where the risk of developing schizophrenia increases three fold,true,237,31,6.580645161290323,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,-0.0772,"('the national academy of medicine points', 'ORG'), ('marijuana', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')",3
Tom Cotton,becerra supports bernie s government takeover of your health care  eliminating your employer provided coverage,true,110,15,6.333333333333333,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.6908,"('bernie s', 'PERSON')",1
Tom Wolf,we re the only major gas producing state in the us that doesn t have a severance tax,true,84,18,3.7222222222222223,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('us', 'GPE'), ('doesn', 'GPE')",2
Cory Booker,there is a direct connection between discriminatory policies within the usda and the enormous land loss we have seen among black farmers over the past century,true,158,26,5.115384615384615,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.3182,"('the past century', 'DATE')",1
Beto O'Rourke,energy experts and state house dems  among others  were warning of this  the texas power blackout  for years,true,108,18,4.833333333333333,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.0772,"('dems', 'NORP'), ('texas', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE')",3
Facebook posts,the texas power grid is not part of the us power grid because they wanted to avoid federal regulation,true,101,19,4.368421052631579,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.296,"('texas', 'GPE'), ('us', 'GPE')",2
Gordon Hintz,we know mask mandates work  there s enough evidence out there between counties that have done it and counties that haven t,true,122,22,4.545454545454546,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,,0
Chuck Grassley,insulin prices have  gone thru the roof for patients taxpayers bc of manufacturer  health plan   pbm biz practices,true,114,18,5.166666666666667,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,,0
Jenna Wadsworth,north carolina secretary of state elaine marshall  has won more statewide races than probably anyone else alive,true,111,17,5.529411764705882,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.743,"('north carolina', 'GPE')",1
Jennifer Boysko,the united states is the only industrialized  modernized country that does not already have a paid family medical leave program in place,true,136,22,5.181818181818182,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.3818,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1
Marco Rubio,says joe biden  has issued more executive fiats than anyone in such a short period of time  ever  more than obama  more than trump  more than anyone,true,148,27,4.333333333333333,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,0.0,"('joe biden  ', 'PERSON')",1
Pat Toomey,there will be several thousand dollars in payments going to families with six figure incomes who ve had no income interruption whatsoever,true,137,22,5.2727272727272725,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.5719,"('several thousand dollars', 'MONEY'), ('six', 'CARDINAL')",2
Kirk Cox,virginia ranks  in the bottom third of states  in administering the covid    vaccine,true,84,13,5.153846153846154,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('virginia', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')",2
Devin LeMahieu,it takes quite a while on election day to load those ballots  which is why we have the   a m  or   a m  ballot dumping in milwaukee,true,131,27,3.6296296296296298,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.3182,"('election day', 'DATE'), ('milwaukee', 'GPE')",2
Sarah Godlewski,it wasn t all women that lost jobs  in the december jobs report   it was mostly black and latina women  in fact  white women gained employment,true,142,26,4.3076923076923075,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.0772,"('december', 'DATE')",1
Jake Tapper,the second presidential impeachment of donald trump was  the most bipartisan impeachment in american history,true,108,15,6.2,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('american', 'NORP')",2
Sherrod Brown,summer  protesters outside the white house were met with tear gas  rubber bullets  a full militarized response  while     rioters were able to breach the capitol,true,161,25,5.16,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.2263,"('summer', 'DATE'), ('the white house', 'ORG')",2
Kim Reynolds,before covid      more iowans  were  working than at any other time in our state history,true,88,15,4.466666666666667,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('iowans', 'NORP')",1
Mitch McConnell,this election actually was not unusually close,true,46,7,5.714285714285714,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,,0
Joe Biden,in more than    cases  judges  looked at the allegations that trump was making and determined they were without any merit,true,121,20,4.85,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0176,,0
Mike Gallagher,congress has one job here  to count electoral votes that have in fact been cast by any state,true,92,18,4.111111111111111,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('congress', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",2
Pat Toomey,in my state  as in many other states  we have governors who are closing down businesses again,true,93,17,4.411764705882353,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0
Chris Larson,jurisdictions representing about     of wi residents have passed referendums or resolutions in favor of fair maps,true,113,16,5.875,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.6124,,0
Mike Gallagher,new data shows in person learning isn t driving spikes in cases,true,63,12,4.333333333333333,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0
Tim Carpenter,wisconsin is one of the few states that doesn t allow absentee ballots to be processed before election day,true,106,19,4.631578947368421,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.0516,"('wisconsin', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('doesn', 'GPE'), ('election day', 'DATE')",4
JB Pritzker,republican elected officials  a network of propaganda publications in the state and some radio shock jocks  were spreading  a lie  about his daughter breaking covid    restrictions,true,180,26,5.6923076923076925,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.5574,"('republican', 'NORP')",1
Mandy Cohen,says covid    has killed more north carolinians in a year than the flu has in    years,true,86,16,4.0625,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.7964,"('a year', 'DATE')",1
Ralph Northam,people of color and those of not  they use marijuana at the same rate  people of color are three times more likely to get arrested and convicted,true,144,27,4.296296296296297,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.4767,"('marijuana', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')",2
X posts,when donald trump lost the iowa caucus to ted cruz in        he immediately cried that cruz cheated,true,99,17,4.470588235294118,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.802,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('iowa', 'GPE')",2
Tammy Baldwin,we heard from the department of homeland security     that this was probably the most secure election that s ever been run in the united states,true,143,25,4.6,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.7841,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1
Joe Biden,i ve released    years of my tax returns  you can go online and look   donald trump  hasn t released one,true,104,20,3.9,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",2
Theresa Greenfield,farm bankruptcies are  at an eight year high,true,44,8,4.5,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('an eight year', 'DATE')",1
Roy Cooper,says dan forest has  missed almost half of the board of education meetings during the pandemic,true,94,16,4.875,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.296,"('dan forest', 'PERSON'), ('almost half', 'CARDINAL')",2
Robyn Vining,my      election was the first time speaker robin vos has lost a republican held seat,true,85,15,4.4,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.3182,"('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('robin vos', 'PERSON'), ('republican', 'NORP')",3
Facebook posts,joe biden  wants to get rid of something called  stepped up basis   that reduces inheritance taxes,true,98,16,4.9375,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('joe biden  ', 'PERSON')",1
Chris Jacobs,while serving as town supervisor  nate mcmurray voted to raise taxes on homeowners,true,82,13,5.3076923076923075,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0
Robert Ortt,with the ongoing pandemic  our state park attendance is at the highest it s ever been,true,85,16,4.3125,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,,0
Ted Cruz,in       more journalists were killed in mexico than in any other country in the world,true,86,15,4.4,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.6969,"('mexico', 'GPE')",1
John Cornyn,americans died of an overdose in a single year,true,46,9,4.222222222222222,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.5574,"('americans', 'NORP'), ('a single year', 'DATE')",2
Jennifer McClellan,more than half of virginia s school buildings are older than    years,true,69,12,4.583333333333333,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('more than half', 'CARDINAL'), ('virginia', 'GPE')",2
Tony Evers,says he has issued more pardons than  any wisconsin governor in contemporary history,true,84,13,5.461538461538462,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.3597,,0
Brian Tyler Cohen,iowa republicans have introduced a bill that would put government installed cameras in every single classroom to livestream school activities for parents to spy on teachers and children,true,185,28,5.642857142857143,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.0,"('iowa', 'GPE'), ('republicans', 'NORP')",2
Joni Ernst,in iowa   since we have put a number of the voting laws into place over the last several years   voter id is one of those   we ve actually seen voter participation increase  even in off election years,true,200,37,4.243243243243243,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,0.3818,"('iowa', 'GPE'), ('the last several years', 'DATE'), ('election years', 'DATE')",3
Roger Williams,the number of covid    deaths recorded so far in      has surpassed the total for,true,81,14,4.285714285714286,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0772,,0
Jen Psaki,you are    times more likely to go to the hospital if you re not vaccinated     times more likely to die,true,104,20,3.9,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.6326,,0
Iowa Senate Democrats,gov  kim reynolds  touting      million for iowa broadband   failed to mention these are actually federal funds approved by rep  cindy axne and signed into law by president joe biden,true,182,29,4.9655172413793105,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,-0.296,"('gov  kim reynolds  touting', 'PERSON'), ('cindy axne', 'PERSON'), ('joe biden', 'PERSON')",3
NYS Department of Corrections and Community Supervision,new york is  leading the nation with the lowest imprisonment rate of any large state,true,84,15,4.6,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.3818,"('new york', 'GPE')",1
David Gura,fun fact  west virginia is home to zero billionaires,true,52,9,4.777777777777778,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.5106,"('west virginia', 'GPE'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL')",2
Kelda Helen Roys,says gubernatorial candidate rebecca kleefisch  worked with scott walker to sign five abortion restrictions into law that took away services and threatened doctors with prison time for providing safe and legal abortions,true,219,32,5.84375,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,-0.4404,"('five', 'CARDINAL')",1
David McKinley,overdose deaths in wv are up     from the prior year,true,52,10,3.9,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('the prior year', 'DATE')",1
Chris Larson,the gop controlled legislature has  refused to act on at least      appointees of gov  tony evers,true,97,16,4.6875,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.296,"('gop', 'ORG')",1
Mitt Romney,the trump administration worked to free       taliban prisoners,true,63,8,6.25,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('taliban', 'ORG')",1
Mandela Barnes,in afghanistan   over     billion dollars spent on military contracts,true,69,9,6.111111111111111,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,"('afghanistan', 'GPE')",1
Chip Roy,a quorum breaking texas democrat said in      that mail in ballot fraud  is the greatest source of voter fraud in this state,true,124,22,4.409090909090909,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.5267,"('texas', 'GPE'), ('democrat', 'NORP')",2
Mandela Barnes,it s been over    years since minimum  wage  and inflation parted ways  then over a decade since the federal minimum went up at all,true,131,24,4.25,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.0,,0
Glenn Grothman,we have a record     million job openings in the u s,true,52,11,3.4545454545454546,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('the u s', 'FAC')",1
Mark Born,before the pandemic  just over        were on continuing ui claims  now  there are well over         on state or federal ui benefits,true,132,21,4.476190476190476,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.5719,,0
Liquid Death,in georgia  it s  illegal to give people water within     feet of a polling place  and  punishable by up to a year in prison,true,124,24,3.875,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.8689,"('georgia', 'GPE'), ('up to a year', 'DATE')",2
Jevin Hodge,david schweikert has  been convicted of    house ethics violations,true,66,9,6.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.5267,"('david schweikert', 'PERSON')",1
A Better Wisconsin Together,says tim michels  opposes closing the loophole that allows domestic abusers to buy guns,true,87,14,5.214285714285714,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.5574,"('tim michels', 'PERSON')",1
West Virginia Republican Party,overdoses reached an all time high in,true,37,7,4.428571428571429,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.1027,,0
Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee,herschel walker misled about  personally treating       veterans per year   about  graduating from college  and about  working in law enforcement,true,145,19,6.052631578947368,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('herschel walker', 'PERSON')",1
Kathy Hoffman,since       i ve successfully lobbied for the funds to add hundreds of school counselors  lowering our student to school counselor ratio by,true,139,22,5.045454545454546,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.296,"('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')",1
Elizabeth Warren,of the folks who have student loans do not have a college diploma  four year diploma  these are people who are truck drivers and who are nail technicians and nurses  aides,true,171,31,4.451612903225806,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,0.0,"('four year', 'DATE')",1
League of Conservation Voters,says republican u s  sen  ron johnson  called climate change  bull      during a record heatwave  and  raked in over     k in fossil fuel cash,true,142,24,4.333333333333333,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.0,"('republican', 'NORP'), ('ron johnson', 'PERSON')",2
Francesca Hong,in the wisconsin state assembly this session  more than     of gop bills received a public hearing  meanwhile  the gop allowed less than    of democratic bills to have a hearing,true,177,29,4.793103448275862,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,0.0,"('the wisconsin state assembly', 'ORG'), ('gop', 'ORG'), ('gop', 'ORG'), ('democratic', 'NORP')",4
Greg Abbott,texas  public high school graduation rate is at     overall,true,59,9,5.111111111111111,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('texas', 'GPE')",1
Abigail Spanberger,the four big meat packers are raking in record profits,true,54,10,4.5,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.4404,"('four', 'CARDINAL')",1
Levar Stoney,in virginia  black people are eight times   x  more likely than white people to die of gun homicide,true,99,18,4.333333333333333,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.743,"('virginia', 'GPE'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL')",2
Tony Evers,wisconsin s archaic abortion ban is older than    states,true,56,9,5.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.5574,"('wisconsin s archaic abortion ban', 'ORG')",1
Democratic Party of Wisconsin,the tax carve out  ron  johnson spearheaded overwhelmingly benefited the wealthiest  over small businesses,true,106,14,6.428571428571429,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.4019,"('ron  johnson', 'PERSON')",1
Gary Black,in       when raphael warnock ran a campaign ad featuring himself with a beagle   that wasn t his dog,true,101,18,4.222222222222222,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('raphael', 'NORP')",1
Kelda Helen Roys,because of u s  senate rules  democrats need  more than a majority     to codify roe vs  wade,true,93,17,4.0588235294117645,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('senate', 'ORG'), ('democrats', 'NORP')",2
Eric Toney,the state crime lab under attorney general josh kaul  is testing significantly less items than former ag brad schimel and is still taking longer to test many categories of key items in comparison to schimel  including dna,true,221,37,4.945945945945946,30.0,30.0,30.0,30.0,30.0,-0.5423,"('josh kaul  ', 'PERSON'), ('brad schimel', 'PERSON')",2
Lee Zeldin,new york leads the u s  in population loss,true,42,9,3.6666666666666665,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.3182,"('new york', 'GPE')",1
Keith Pekau,we ve reduced crime to its lowest level in    years,true,51,10,3.9,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.7269,,0
Kathy Hochul,since taking office  hochul has passed more than     new bills,true,62,10,4.8,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,,0
Melissa Agard,cannabis reform  is supported by the majority of the residents of our state  including a majority of republicans,true,112,18,5.166666666666667,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.3182,"('republicans', 'NORP')",1
Jennifer Konfrst,only    of k    students would benefit from iowa s school voucher bill,true,70,12,4.416666666666667,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.4588,,0
Tim Kaine,virginia women are paid    cents for every dollar paid to virginia men,true,70,12,4.666666666666667,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('virginia', 'GPE'), ('virginia', 'GPE')",2
Kathy Hochul,we are no    among all large states in having fully vaccinated teenagers  we are no    in all large states for having fully vaccinated five  to     year olds,true,157,27,4.407407407407407,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.5267,"('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('year olds', 'DATE')",2
Glenn Grothman,the us has made strides in reducing carbon emissions that other parts of the world have not,true,91,17,4.411764705882353,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('us', 'GPE')",1
Kamala Harris,black women in the u s  are  three to four times more likely to die in connection with childbirth than other women,true,114,22,4.136363636363637,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.6326,"('three to four', 'CARDINAL')",1
Byron Donalds,kamala harris  co sponsored  fully sponsored  the green new deal,true,64,10,5.2,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('kamala harris  ', 'PERSON')",1
David Crowley,under  the biden  administration we have witnessed the fastest growth of black owned small businesses in more than    years,true,123,19,5.2631578947368425,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.3818,"('more than    years', 'DATE')",1
Tony Evers,wisconsin had a  record breaking year  for tourism in,true,53,9,4.777777777777778,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'ORG')",1
Social Media,under federal law  former president donald trump s  felony convictions mean he can no longer possess guns,true,105,17,5.117647058823529,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.6908,"('donald trump', 'PERSON')",1
Joe Biden,violent crime is near a record    year low,true,42,8,4.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.8591,,0
Tyler August,nearly     of all uw graduates stay in wisconsin   years after they graduate,true,76,12,4.916666666666667,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE')",2
Mark Pocan,we passed    bills last year  which is the fewest since the depression,true,70,12,4.583333333333333,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.5719,"('last year', 'DATE')",1
Lisa Subeck,the united states is an outlier  one of only about half a dozen countries  without any guarantee of paid leave for new parents and or other health care needs,true,157,29,4.379310344827586,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.6199,"('the united states', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('only about half a dozen', 'CARDINAL')",3
Brian Schimming,we ve had    elections in    years in wisconsin that have been decided by less than        votes,true,96,16,4.25,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'GPE')",1
Tammy Baldwin,we re facing situations these days where you have to have two officers in the evidence room in case there s an accidental  fentanyl  exposure,true,141,25,4.6,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.0772,"('these days', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')",2
Sarah Godlewski,when it comes to how many votes  president  joe biden won  it was literally less than a few votes per ward,true,106,21,3.9523809523809526,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.5719,"('joe biden', 'PERSON')",1
António Guterres,gaza has  the highest number of people facing catastrophic hunger ever recorded by the integrated food security classification system   anywhere  anytime,true,153,21,6.142857142857143,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.3612,"('gaza', 'GPE')",1
Patrick Burke,the great lakes account for  over     of the world s freshwater and over     of north america s freshwater,true,106,18,4.444444444444445,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.6249,"('north america', 'LOC')",1
Tony Evers,we re having the largest classes of correctional officers we ve ever had before,true,79,14,4.714285714285714,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0
Elise Stefanik,we ve seen an      increase in the swanton sector  which is the part of the northern border that i represent  in illegal crossings,true,130,23,4.391304347826087,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.3182,,0
Kirsten Gillibrand,marijuana is currently classified in the same category of drugs as heroin and a more dangerous category than fentanyl or cocaine,true,128,21,5.142857142857143,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.7645,"('marijuana', 'PERSON')",1
Chris Larson,says expanding medicaid in wisconsin would save the state      million  which could pay for       k    teachers  or     educators per district,true,142,20,5.15,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.4215,"('expanding medicaid', 'PERSON'), ('wisconsin', 'GPE')",2
Joe Biden,under joe biden  there are  record numbers of new black entrepreneurs,true,69,11,5.181818181818182,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('joe biden  ', 'PERSON')",1
Kelda Helen Roys,minnesota incarcerates  about a third of what wisconsin does,true,60,9,5.666666666666667,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('minnesota', 'GPE'), ('about a third', 'CARDINAL'), ('wisconsin', 'GPE')",3
Kamala Harris,postpartum medicaid coverage expanded from three states to    states because of the biden administration,true,104,14,6.285714285714286,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('postpartum medicaid', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')",2
Tammy Baldwin,wisconsin had over       opioid overdose deaths in,true,50,7,5.428571428571429,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'ORG')",1
Scott Walker,the  top issue for college students is the economy,true,50,9,4.555555555555555,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.2023,,0
Tony Evers,in april last year  our state unemployment rate hit a record low of       last year  wisconsin had an all time lowest number of unemployed workers ever in modern history,true,169,29,4.586206896551724,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,-0.743,"('april last year', 'DATE'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('wisconsin', 'GPE')",3
Kamala Harris,today in america    in   women of reproductive age live in a state with an abortion ban,true,87,16,4.1875,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.5574,"('today', 'DATE')",1
Ron DeSantis,donald trump  deported less  believe it or not  than barack obama even did,true,74,13,4.538461538461538,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('donald trump', 'PERSON')",1
Nikki Haley,we ve had more americans die of fentanyl than the iraq  afghanistan  and vietnam wars  combined,true,95,16,4.8125,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.8307,"('americans', 'NORP'), ('iraq', 'GPE'), ('afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('vietnam', 'EVENT')",4
Jill Billings,with school based professional social workers  the recommendation is     to    and in wisconsin  we re almost triple that,true,121,18,5.277777777777778,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'GPE')",1
Marianne Williamson,we sell arms to     of the world s autocrats  we are the world s largest arms exporters,true,87,17,3.8823529411764706,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,,0
Ted Cruz,we produce a lot more wind energy in texas than california does,true,63,12,4.333333333333333,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.3353,"('texas', 'GPE'), ('california', 'GPE')",2
Bloggers,whole of italy goes into quarantine,true,35,6,5.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,0.0,"('italy', 'GPE')",1
Roger Roth,the average  wisconsin  resident s tax burden is at its lowest level in nearly    years while incomes continue to grow,true,118,20,4.7,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.6705,"('nearly    years', 'DATE')",1
Michael Bloomberg,during his tenure as mayor of new york city   street homelessness decreased by    percent,true,89,14,5.071428571428571,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('new york city', 'GPE')",1
Jane O’Meara Sanders,berniesanders receives strong support from the conservative   most rural part of vermont,true,88,12,6.25,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.7184,"('vermont', 'GPE')",1
Amy Klobuchar,the majority of hunters now want universal background checks  the majority of trump voters,true,90,14,5.428571428571429,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0772,,0
Joe Biden,from the moment we passed that signature legislation  mike  bloomberg  called it a disgrace,true,91,14,5.357142857142857,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.4939,"('mike', 'PERSON'), ('bloomberg  called', 'PERSON')",2
Tom Barrett,says since he took office  the city of milwaukee has seen the creation of       new affordable housing units,true,108,18,4.666666666666667,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.2732,"('milwaukee', 'GPE')",1
Cory Booker,national polls have  never predicted who will be president from our party  carter was in the single digits a few months before caucuses  bill clinton was  obama      points behind in the national polls roughly,true,209,34,4.911764705882353,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,0.4019,"('a few months', 'DATE'), ('bill clinton', 'PERSON')",2
Jake Tapper,traditionally  the speaker says   members of congress  i have the high privilege and distinct honor of presenting to you the president of the united states    tonight  speaker pelosi said   members of congress  the president of the united states,true,245,38,5.184210526315789,30.0,30.0,30.0,30.0,30.0,0.8834,"('congress', 'ORG'), ('the united states', 'GPE'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('congress', 'ORG'), ('the united states', 'GPE')",5
James White,says      of u s  children are texans,true,37,7,3.5714285714285716,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('texans', 'NORP')",1
Elizabeth Warren,the president of the united states already has the legal authority to reduce the price of many commonly used prescription drugs,true,127,21,5.095238095238095,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.5574,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1
Pete Buttigieg,more than     of republicans think we ought to at least be doing universal background checks,true,92,15,4.933333333333334,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('republicans', 'NORP')",1
Michael Bloomberg,mayor bloomberg helped lower the number of uninsured by    percent  covering         more new yorkers,true,101,14,5.428571428571429,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.2263,"('bloomberg', 'PERSON')",1
Facebook posts,twitter is banned in iran,true,25,5,4.2,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,-0.4588,"('iran', 'GPE')",1
Tammy Baldwin,witnesses have been part of  every other impeachment trial the senate has ever had,true,82,14,4.857142857142857,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('senate', 'ORG')",1
Andrew Cuomo,we have the lowest corporate tax rate since,true,43,8,4.5,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.3818,,0
Facebook posts,florida is  the   th in state education funding,true,47,8,4.625,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('florida', 'GPE')",1
Facebook posts,in       in response to iran s attack on the u s s  samuel roberts  president ronald reagan  destroyed half of iran s navy,true,122,23,3.9565217391304346,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.743,"('iran', 'GPE'), ('the u s s  samuel', 'PRODUCT'), ('ronald reagan', 'PERSON'), ('half', 'CARDINAL')",4
Bernie Sanders,we end the      billion a year that the health care industry makes,true,66,12,4.166666666666667,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.4939,"('the      billion', 'LAW')",1
Elizabeth Warren,look at the men on this stage  collectively  they have lost    elections  the only people on this stage who have won every single election that they ve been in are the women  amy and me,true,185,35,4.114285714285714,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,0.34,,0
Viral image,a man at  the storming of the u s  embassy  in iraq visited the white house in,true,78,17,3.4705882352941178,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('iraq', 'GPE'), ('the white house', 'ORG')",2
Elizabeth Warren,last year     million americans didn t have a prescription filled because they couldn t afford it,true,97,16,4.875,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('last year', 'DATE'), ('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('americans', 'NORP')",3
Andrew Yang,if you re a black woman  you re      more likely to die from complications in childbirth,true,88,16,4.1875,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.6326,,0
Bernie Sanders,real wages  went up last year,true,29,6,3.8333333333333335,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,"('last year', 'DATE')",1
Joe Biden,california firefighters decided  to speak out  against president trump because his tweet about the state s wildfires  contained so much misinformation,true,150,21,6.0476190476190474,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.3774,"('california', 'GPE')",1
Jim Justice,says a new annual report shows that  west virginia s tourism industry has grown for the second consecutive year  reversing years of decline and outpacing national growth by    percent,true,183,29,5.172413793103448,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,0.3818,"('annual', 'DATE'), ('west virginia', 'GPE'), ('the second consecutive year  reversing years', 'DATE')",3
Mark Walker,says the cartels are so bad in a mexican border state that the u s  government issued a  do not travel  warning    the same warning it issued for syria,true,151,29,4.0344827586206895,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,-0.3441,"('mexican', 'NORP'), ('syria', 'GPE')",2
Ron Kind,i am the only member of congress that voted for both inquiries    the clinton inquiry and now the trump inquiry,true,111,20,4.45,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('congress', 'ORG'), ('clinton', 'PERSON')",2
Elizabeth Warren,if we make no changes over the next    years  americans will reach into their pockets and pay out about     trillion on insurance premiums  copays  deductibles and uncovered medical expenses,true,190,29,5.241379310344827,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.3612,"('the next    years', 'DATE'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2
Shelley Moore Capito,on average  one person dies by suicide every    hours in west virginia,true,70,12,4.583333333333333,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.6705,"('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('every    hours', 'TIME'), ('west virginia', 'GPE')",3
Darrell Steinberg,californians are unsheltered and homeless,true,41,5,7.4,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,0.0,"('californians', 'NORP')",1
Pete Buttigieg,americans  say that what they want is a choice  to join a single payer system like medicare rather than ending private insurance,true,128,22,4.7727272727272725,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.6124,"('americans', 'NORP'), ('medicare', 'ORG')",2
Joe Manchin,west virginia department of education reported over        children and youth have been identified as homeless for the           school year,true,140,19,5.526315789473684,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('west virginia', 'GPE')",1
Glenn Grothman,millionaires are eligible for food stamps  but  donald trump came along and decided to put a stop to it,true,103,19,4.368421052631579,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.4215,,0
David McKinley,about    percent of america s production of ethylene is produced on the gulf coast in texas and louisiana,true,105,18,4.722222222222222,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('the gulf coast', 'LOC'), ('texas', 'GPE'), ('louisiana', 'GPE')",3
Josh Hawley,meth production in mo has cratered over last decade  mo hwy patrol reported       meth lab seizures in       only    in,true,119,19,4.473684210526316,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,"('mo', 'GPE'), ('last decade', 'DATE')",2
Donald Trump,minneapolis  city government preemptively informed the target center that it would be responsible for          in security and other costs  related to a trump rally   more than    times the estimated security costs for a      target center health care rally held by president barack obama,true,288,43,5.232558139534884,33.0,33.0,33.0,33.0,33.0,0.8519,"('minneapolis', 'GPE')",1
Donald Trump,says in the      presidential election   i won that one by    points       points    west virginia,true,98,14,4.714285714285714,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.5719,"('west virginia', 'GPE')",1
Gwen Moore,more than half of death row prisoners are people of color,true,57,11,4.2727272727272725,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.802,"('more than half', 'CARDINAL')",1
Roy Blunt,u s  agricultural   food exports are expected to increase more than    billion annually under  usmca,true,100,15,5.266666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.3182,"('more than    billion', 'MONEY'), ('annually', 'DATE')",2
Josh Kaul,says people convicted of felonies or under restraining orders  can buy a firearm without going through a background check,true,121,19,5.368421052631579,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.5423,,0
Sheldon Whitehouse,one unnamed donor gave     million to the leo affiliated judicial crisis network to block the nomination of judge merrick garland and to support gorsuch  then a donor   perhaps the same one   gave another     million to prop up kavanaugh,true,237,38,4.921052631578948,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,-0.6486,"('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('merrick garland', 'PERSON'), ('another     million', 'CARDINAL')",3
Arlen Parsa,thirty four of the    men depicted in the famous  declaration of independence  painting were slaveholders,true,105,15,5.733333333333333,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('thirty four', 'CARDINAL')",1
Beto O'Rourke,there are     million guns out on the streets of a country of     million people,true,80,14,4.214285714285714,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,,0
Samuel Sinyangwe,america has more governors who ve worn blackface than black governors,true,69,11,5.363636363636363,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.296,"('america', 'GPE')",1
Whoopi Goldberg,the last time people  created a hollywood blacklist   people ended up killing themselves   they were accused  and they lost their right to work,true,143,23,5.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.7845,,0
Dave Aronberg,florida s red flag gun law has been used  about five times a day,true,64,14,3.5714285714285716,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.34,"('florida', 'GPE'), ('about five', 'CARDINAL')",2
Elizabeth Warren,the law says that mental health must be treated the same as physical health   but coverage by health insurers is unequal,true,120,21,4.666666666666667,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.4767,,0
Michael Bloomberg,if you go back  you can see wayne lapierre  who runs the nra  testifying in front of congress in favor of background checks    or    years ago,true,142,26,4.153846153846154,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.4019,"('congress', 'ORG')",1
Bobby Scott,studies show at the minimum wage  you can t rent a two bedroom apartment anywhere in the united states   a modest  two bedroom apartment,true,136,24,4.541666666666667,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.4215,"('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('the united states', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')",3
Amy Klobuchar,big pharmaceuticals pay off   they literally pay off   generics to keep the prices and the competition off the market,true,117,19,5.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.2023,,0
Stony Rushing,says    out of     gop candidates don t live in north carolina s  th congressional district,true,91,15,4.6,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('gop', 'ORG'), ('north carolina', 'GPE')",2
Bernie Sanders,in my own state of vermont  from the very first days of our state s history  what our constitution says is that everybody can vote  that is true  so people in jail can vote,true,172,34,3.9705882352941178,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,0.4215,"('vermont', 'GPE'), ('the very first days', 'DATE')",2
Joe Manchin,i was the only member of the senate   republican or democrat   who has consistently voted against efforts to use the so called  nuclear option  to change the rules of the senate,true,177,31,4.548387096774194,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,0.0,"('senate', 'ORG'), ('republican', 'NORP'), ('democrat', 'NORP'), ('senate', 'ORG')",4
West Virginia Republican Party,west virginia s exports increased for the second year in a row in       reaching      billion  additionally  west virginia s export growth rate was        nearly double the national average of,true,192,29,4.9655172413793105,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,0.6705,"('west virginia', 'GPE'), ('the second year in a row', 'DATE'), ('west virginia', 'GPE')",3
E. Gordon Gee,our state has fewer science  technology  engineering and math graduates than any neighboring state,true,98,14,5.928571428571429,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,,0
Mac Heller,the      election was the first election in which voters of color comprised over    percent of the electorate  and that number is going up,true,138,23,4.6521739130434785,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0772,"('first', 'ORDINAL')",1
Allen Thomas,currently     percent of our military s infrastructure is graded as  poor  while   percent is  failing,true,102,15,5.266666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.7506,,0
Donald Trump,in new york state  democrats blocked a bill expanding college tuition for gold star families after approving aid for illegal immigrants,true,135,21,5.428571428571429,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.6908,"('new york', 'GPE'), ('democrats', 'NORP')",2
West Virginia Democratic Party,the affordable care act  provided over         west virginians with health care coverage,true,88,12,5.666666666666667,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.7506,"('west virginians', 'NORP')",1
Shelia Stubbs,wisconsin  has  the highest infant mortality rate for black babies nationwide,true,77,11,5.909090909090909,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'GPE')",1
John Torbett,says all north carolina teachers do not currently get a  duty free lunch break,true,78,14,4.571428571428571,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.5106,"('north carolina', 'GPE')",1
Clif Smart,missouri ranks   th in the nation in per capita state fiscal support for higher education and missouri state is last among missouri schools,true,139,23,5.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.4019,"('missouri', 'GPE'), ('missouri', 'GPE'), ('missouri', 'GPE')",3
Daniel Riemer,about    percent of  the manufacturing and agriculture  tax credit goes to claimants who are making    million or more,true,118,18,5.166666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.3818,,0
Kirsten Gillibrand,for cabinet posts   i have the best voting record against trump nominees of anyone else running for president,true,109,18,5.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.6369,,0
Quentin Miller,says an ice detainer request  is not a valid warrant,true,52,10,4.2,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0
Tammy Baldwin,states still don t have  comprehensive protections  for people in the lgbtq community,true,85,13,5.461538461538462,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.25,,0
Tommie Pierson Jr.,says  zero  african americans have presented to the house budget committee in,true,77,12,5.333333333333333,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('african americans', 'NORP'), ('the house budget committee', 'ORG')",3
Mike Parson,we are always going to need architects  doctors  we re going to need professionals with four year degrees  but    to    percent of the people in missouri don t have degrees,true,172,30,4.466666666666667,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.0,"('four year', 'DATE'), ('missouri', 'GPE')",2
Elizabeth Warren,the boeing     max    the type of plane that crashed in ethiopia  continues to fly in the united states  despite the faa saying  software updates are likely coming,true,163,27,4.703703703703703,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,0.4215,"('max', 'PERSON'), ('ethiopia', 'GPE'), ('the united states', 'GPE')",3
Phil Berger,since       the gap in high school graduation rates between african american students and all students has been cut in half  from     percent to     percent,true,156,24,4.916666666666667,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.2732,"('african', 'NORP'), ('american', 'NORP'), ('half', 'CARDINAL')",3
Chris Jones,virginia house  republicans have had more african americans on key committees than when the democrats were in control,true,117,18,5.5,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('virginia', 'GPE'), ('republicans', 'NORP'), ('african americans', 'NORP'), ('democrats', 'NORP')",4
E. Gordon Gee,west virginia has  the nation s lowest workforce participation rate  which hovers around    percent  when the national average is about    percent,true,146,21,5.571428571428571,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.3818,"('west virginia', 'GPE')",1
Monica Wallace,significantly more people died of covid    in two months than died of overdoses all of last year or the year before,true,115,21,4.380952380952381,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.8297,"('two months', 'DATE'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('the year', 'DATE')",3
Desiree Rogers,in covid    crisis   only     of african americans had jobs where they could work from home,true,91,15,4.533333333333333,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.6249,"('african', 'NORP'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2
George Borrello,infection rates in allegany  cattaraugus and chautauqua counties have consistently been among the lowest in the state,true,117,17,5.882352941176471,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.3818,,0
Sara Meaney,since the week ending march     wisconsin actually saw a drop in tourism spending compared to last year of      billion,true,119,19,4.842105263157895,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.2732,"('the week ending march', 'DATE'), ('wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE')",3
Planned Parenthood,if roe is overturned  wisconsin has a law on the books that would immediately make abortion a crime,true,99,18,4.5,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.5423,"('wisconsin', 'GPE')",1
Joe Biden,today  the gap between african american and white homeownership is larger than it was in the late     s,true,103,18,4.5,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('today', 'DATE'), ('african', 'NORP'), ('american', 'NORP'), ('white homeownership', 'ORG')",4
Glenn Grothman,research illustrates a clear correlation between vitamin d deficiencies and  higher  covid    mortality rates,true,109,14,6.5,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.5859,,0
Darren Jackson,two thirds of americans disapprove of donald trump not wearing a face mask in public,true,84,15,4.666666666666667,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('two thirds', 'CARDINAL'), ('americans', 'NORP'), ('donald trump', 'PERSON')",3
Facebook posts,says gloves shouldn t be worn in public because  if you are wearing the same set of gloves all over town you are only spreading germs everywhere you go,true,151,29,4.206896551724138,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.296,,0
American Automobile Association,new york is one of only    states where the average gallon of gas costs more than,true,81,16,3.9375,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('new york', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('gallon', 'CARDINAL')",3
Chris Kapenga,says it s illegal to hold an absentee only election or mail ballots to every registered voter,true,93,17,4.529411764705882,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.6908,,0
Jamie Nadler,small trials  to test convalescent plasma therapy for coronavirus patients  seem to have had some degree of success,true,115,18,5.333333333333333,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.5719,,0
Veronica Escobar,says texas  either is near the bottom or at the very bottom when it comes to testing per capita,true,95,19,4.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('texas', 'GPE')",1
Levar Stoney,virginia has  lagged behind other states when it comes to  covid     testing,true,76,12,4.916666666666667,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.296,"('virginia', 'GPE')",1
Joe Biden,until this week  they  osha  weren t even enforcing these guidelines  for coronavirus   still today  osha is not specifying which rules employees must follow or how to keep their workers safe and healthy,true,203,33,4.96969696969697,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,0.6808,"('this week', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE')",2
Facebook posts,the poor are  ironically  the most likely to be employed in the industries deemed  essential  while their upper class peers are freed to bunker down for weeks until the first death wave passes,true,192,33,4.7272727272727275,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,-0.6486,"('weeks', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')",2
Andrew Cuomo,go look at other countries that went through exactly this  started to reopen  and then they saw the infection rate go back up again,true,131,24,4.416666666666667,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.0,,0
Facebook posts,africans living in china now being forced to sleep outside in the cold  as  chinese nationals blame them for the rising number of new coronavirus cases in the country,true,166,29,4.689655172413793,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.6249,"('africans', 'NORP'), ('china', 'GPE'), ('chinese', 'NORP')",3
Barack Obama,republicans  have shown themselves willing to cut millions off their health insurance and eliminate preexisting condition protections for millions more  even in the middle of this public health crisis,true,200,29,5.862068965517241,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.7351,"('republicans', 'NORP'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')",3
John Bel Edwards,says of the coronavirus threat   there was not a single suggestion by anyone  a doctor  a scientist  a political figure  that we needed to cancel mardi gras,true,156,27,4.592592592592593,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.6597,,0
Viral image,photo shows a crowded new york city subway train during stay at home order,true,74,14,4.357142857142857,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('new york city', 'GPE')",1
Pat Toomey,my mask will keep someone else safe and their mask will keep me safe,true,68,14,3.9285714285714284,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.7003,,0
Andrew Cuomo,no city in the state can quarantine itself without state approval,true,65,11,5.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.5795,,0
Kelly Alexander,says  most  nc legislators are in the  high risk age group  for coronavirus,true,75,13,4.538461538461538,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.2732,,0
Viral image,says spectrum will provide free internet to students during coronavirus school closures,true,87,12,6.333333333333333,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.5106,,0
Jim Justice,west virginia has one of the greatest percentages of veterans in any state,true,74,13,4.769230769230769,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.6369,"('west virginia', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",2
Facebook posts,wisconsin republicans have not passed a single bill in   months,true,63,10,5.2,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('republicans', 'NORP'), ('months', 'DATE')",3
Joe Biden,the president s own fbi director said that the greatest domestic terrorist threat is white supremacists,true,103,16,5.5,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.7096,"('fbi', 'ORG')",1
Phil Scott,that     wealth tax  starts at          per family,true,50,7,4.285714285714286,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.4939,,0
Michael Burgess,in the last    years less than half of adults in the u s  received a flu shot,true,77,17,3.3529411764705883,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.3818,"('the last    years', 'DATE'), ('less than half', 'CARDINAL')",2
Joe Biden,iran has stockpiled    times as much enriched uranium as it had  in,true,67,12,4.333333333333333,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('iran', 'GPE')",1
Nick Freitas,abigail spanberger  has voted with nancy pelosi over     of the time,true,68,11,4.818181818181818,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('abigail spanberger', 'PERSON'), ('nancy', 'PERSON')",2
Facebook posts,video showed police thank  kyle rittenhouse    give him water prior to the killings,true,83,13,5.153846153846154,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.4588,,0
National Republican Senatorial Committee,cal cunningham  voted for over    billion in new taxes,true,54,9,4.666666666666667,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,"('cal cunningham', 'ORG'), ('over    billion', 'MONEY')",2
Cory Booker,says the u s  senate is  dominated by millionaires  and that he is  not one of them,true,83,17,3.7058823529411766,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('senate', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",2
Instagram posts,the gop lawyer who helped kanye west get on the ballot in wisconsin is actively working for donald trump s campaign,true,115,21,4.523809523809524,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.3182,"('gop', 'ORG'), ('kanye west', 'PERSON'), ('wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('donald trump s', 'PERSON')",4
M.J. Hegar,says   in   texans did not have health insurance coverage before the pandemic  and now  nearly   in   texans under the age of    don t have access to health care insurance,true,171,29,4.482758620689655,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,0.4939,"('texans', 'NORP'), ('texans', 'NORP')",2
Joe Biden,on home health workers  low pay and limited benefits       are still on snap or medicaid,true,88,15,4.466666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.2023,"('medicaid', 'ORG')",1
Donald Trump,murders this year have spiked     in philadelphia,true,49,7,5.571428571428571,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.6124,"('this year', 'DATE'), ('philadelphia', 'GPE')",2
Public Citizen,taxpayers spent             to develop this drug   remdesivir,true,61,7,5.857142857142857,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,,0
Mike Gallagher,the average family in america forks over more of their hard earned income to their local hospital than to the irs,true,113,21,4.428571428571429,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.1689,"('america', 'GPE'), ('irs', 'ORG')",2
Chris Hayes,higher education is one of america s strongest export sectors  over   million international students studied at american universities   in the          school year  they contributed over     billion to the economy,true,213,29,5.724137931034483,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.4404,"('america', 'GPE'), ('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('american', 'NORP')",3
Ron McMullen,former u s  vice president richard mentor johnson was a slave owner married to one of his slaves and father of two children with her,true,132,25,4.28,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('richard mentor', 'PERSON'), ('johnson', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')",3
John Cornyn,the united states has not completed a  top to bottom review of our criminal justice system at the national level since,true,118,21,4.619047619047619,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.2978,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1
Priorities USA Action,says president trump said coronavirus testing makes the u s  look bad   so i said to my people   slow the testing down,true,118,22,4.181818181818182,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.5423,"('trump', 'PERSON')",1
Facebook posts,says a      milwaukee ymca brochure shows children playing a violent  racist carnival game,true,90,13,5.538461538461538,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.7964,,0
Donald Trump,the poverty rates for african americans and hispanic americans    it s been incredible  they ve all reached their lowest levels in the history of our country,true,157,26,4.923076923076923,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.6705,"('african', 'NORP'), ('americans', 'NORP'), ('hispanic', 'NORP'), ('americans', 'NORP')",4
VoteVets.org,says rick scott s  hospital company stole millions  defrauding the military s health care program,true,97,15,5.4,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.4939,"('rick scott s  hospital', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')",2
Dan McCready,mark harris has said he would abolish the department of education,true,65,11,5.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('mark harris', 'PERSON')",1
Andrew Cuomo,he even supports putting a female inmate in shackles during childbirth,true,70,11,5.454545454545454,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.3612,,0
Beto O'Rourke,says  only one other senator from either party over the last    years  has  a worse record on bipartisanship  than ted cruz,true,123,21,4.571428571428571,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.1027,"('only one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the last    years', 'DATE')",2
Democratic Party of Wisconsin,leah vukmir opposes buy american legislation,true,44,6,6.5,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('american', 'NORP')",1
Ann Wagner,since passage of the tax cuts and jobs act  walmart  increased their starting wage to     hr   has given about      million in bonuses,true,134,22,4.545454545454546,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.5423,"('about      million', 'CARDINAL')",1
Ted Budd,most of kathy manning s donors are from out of state,true,52,11,3.8181818181818183,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,,0
Tim Kaine,the national economy was strong in its largest expansion of private sector jobs before president trump came into office,true,119,19,5.315789473684211,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.5106,,0
Gavin Newsom,close to half of the children  in california are  at or near poverty   when you consider cost of living,true,103,19,4.2631578947368425,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.5106,"('close to half', 'CARDINAL'), ('california', 'GPE')",2
Bloggers,says sean hannity told listeners of his radio show that  beto o rourke is asking for help in getting undocumented to vote,true,121,22,4.5,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.4019,"('sean', 'NORP')",1
Claire McCaskill,says a josh hawley lawsuit  would take away important prescription drug coverage for seniors through medicare and end all of the consumer protections under the aca,true,163,26,5.269230769230769,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.0258,"('medicare', 'ORG'), ('aca', 'ORG')",2
Jeff Merkley,says the trump administration transferred     million from fema to ice,true,70,10,5.7,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('fema', 'ORG')",1
Greg Abbott,says texas  high school graduation rates are at all time highs,true,62,11,4.636363636363637,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('texas', 'GPE')",1
West Virginia Republican Party,for only the second time since       there are more job openings than americans who are unemployed,true,98,16,4.8125,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2
Joe Manchin,this year west virginia produced more americorps members than any other state,true,77,12,5.5,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('this year', 'DATE'), ('west virginia', 'GPE')",2
Tammy Duckworth,if you are a gun store owner and you decide to go out of business   you right now are allowed to convert your entire gun store inventory to  personal use  and once it is a personal use weapon  you can sell it without background checks,true,234,45,4.111111111111111,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,-0.7184,,0
Silvestre Reyes,says beto o rourke  has a criminal record that includes dwi and burglary arrests,true,80,14,4.714285714285714,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.743,,0
Civitas Institute,apple and amazon already operate in many states that require levels of voter id,true,79,14,4.714285714285714,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.1779,,0
Beto O'Rourke,i don t take a dime of pac money,true,32,9,2.6666666666666665,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,,0
Club for Growth,says leah vukmir  claimed the open records law didn t apply to her  got sued  lost and cost taxpayers         in legal fees,true,123,22,4.136363636363637,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.2023,"('leah vukmir', 'PERSON')",1
Jeff Sessions,one out of every    people in the greater boston area is an illegal alien,true,73,14,4.071428571428571,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.2732,"('one', 'CARDINAL')",1
Roger Williams,says he s  never voted  present  in the house instead of taking a yes or no position,true,84,17,3.823529411764706,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.128,,0
Mike Pence,in       ice  arrested more than         illegal immigrants with criminal convictions or facing charges of breaking our nation s  laws   and removed nearly       gang members,true,174,24,5.291666666666667,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.9096,,0
Tim Kaine,in december of       the prince william board of supervisors had a meeting      corey stewart  skipped that meeting to go campaign in alabama for roy moore to be a u s  senator   you haven t disavowed roy moore s name yet,true,221,40,4.175,31.0,31.0,31.0,31.0,31.0,0.0,"('december', 'DATE'), ('william', 'PERSON'), ('corey stewart', 'PERSON'), ('alabama', 'GPE'), ('roy moore s', 'PERSON')",5
Kamala Harris,let s talk about the facts and where we are today  there are still nearly       children who are separated from their parents  due to the trump administration s zero tolerance policy,true,182,31,4.645161290322581,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.296,"('today', 'DATE'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL')",2
Steve McCraw,since       there has been a     reduction in crime in communities at the texas mexico border,true,93,15,4.6,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.5423,"('texas', 'GPE')",1
Facebook posts,rep  ilhan omar  voted yes  to  provide further funding for the      first responders victims fund  while sen  rand paul  voted no,true,130,21,4.666666666666667,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.2023,"('rep  ilhan omar  voted', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('rand paul', 'PERSON')",3
Bloggers,triggering leftists  trump s reelection campaign is selling plastic straws,true,74,10,6.4,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0
Donald Trump,food stamp participation hits    year low,true,41,6,5.5,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.2732,,0
Cory Booker,in       we had more marijuana possession arrests in our country than all other violent crimes combined,true,103,16,5.125,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.7943,"('marijuana', 'PERSON')",1
Bernie Sanders,the wealthiest three families now own more wealth than the bottom half of the country,true,85,15,4.733333333333333,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.7713,"('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('half', 'CARDINAL')",2
Ta-Nehisi Coates,the typical black family in this country has one tenth the wealth of the typical white family,true,93,17,4.529411764705882,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.4939,"('one tenth', 'CARDINAL')",1
Scott Walker,wisconsin is a top    state for health care coverage,true,52,9,4.555555555555555,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.6124,"('wisconsin', 'ORG')",1
Mark Pocan,the united states is the only industrialized country without universal healthcare,true,81,11,6.454545454545454,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.4215,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1
Ron Johnson,just the last three weeks  on average about        women  children  men are coming over across the border illegally as family units or as unaccompanied children,true,160,25,5.04,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.0,"('the last three weeks', 'DATE')",1
Ray Cross,most research shows that  uw salaries  are a little behind  and  in  some areas we re behind more than others,true,109,20,4.25,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,,0
Seth Moulton,the va negotiates prescription drug prices  medicare doesn t do that,true,68,11,5.181818181818182,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('medicare', 'ORG')",1
Tulsi Gabbard,says immigrant military service members applying for u s  citizenship  are getting rejected at higher numbers than those who are not veterans,true,141,22,5.363636363636363,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.5106,,0
John Hickenlooper,we beat the nra with tough  tough gun laws  in colorado,true,55,11,3.909090909090909,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.5267,"('colorado', 'GPE')",1
Kirsten Gillibrand,i actually in      ran on medicare for all,true,42,8,3.75,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,"('medicare', 'ORG')",1
Amy Klobuchar,we ve had a     increase in suicides in this country in just    years,true,69,13,3.8461538461538463,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.3182,"('just    years', 'DATE')",1
Tracy McCreery,suicide is the second leading cause of death among       year olds and       year olds in missouri,true,98,16,4.4375,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.8555,"('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('year olds and', 'DATE'), ('year olds', 'DATE'), ('missouri', 'GPE')",4
Patricia Pike,over    states passed the legislation to ban powdered alcohol   and missouri is not one of them,true,95,16,4.6875,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.5574,"('missouri', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",2
Joe Biden,i m one of the first guys to introduce a climate change bill  way  way back in,true,78,17,3.5294117647058822,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')",2
Ron Johnson,of businesses in wisconsin are small businesses   and they employ  nearly half of our workforce,true,95,15,5.2,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'GPE'), ('nearly half', 'CARDINAL')",2
Donald Trump,the unemployment rate for wisconsin workers has reached historic lows  it s never been this low before  ever  ever  ever,true,120,20,4.85,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.6883,"('wisconsin workers', 'ORG')",1
Letitia James,the enumeration clause speaks to the count of every individual  and not just americans  not just citizens,true,105,17,5.117647058823529,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('americans', 'NORP')",1
Bennett Sandlin,says     of people in texas are  crammed into    of the land,true,60,11,3.8181818181818183,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('texas', 'GPE')",1
Michael Kearns,when i saw corruption and sexual harassment cover ups i called on sheldon silver to resign,true,90,16,4.6875,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.7096,,0
Eric Holcomb,we re growing union jobs faster than illinois,true,45,8,4.75,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.1779,"('illinois', 'GPE')",1
New Leadership PAC,says county parties representing more than half the state s republican voters approved resolutions  demanding changes  in texas house leadership,true,144,20,6.15,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.5574,"('more than half', 'CARDINAL'), ('republican', 'NORP'), ('texas', 'GPE')",3
Delaine Eastin,ninety percent of people born in the     s ended up doing better financially than their parents  but those born in the     s  the much maligned millennials  have only a       chance of doing better  financially  than their parents  despite being the best educated generation in our history,true,289,46,4.869565217391305,33.0,33.0,33.0,33.0,33.0,0.4114,"('ninety percent', 'PERCENT')",1
Mark Pocan,what republicans call the  death tax  is the estate tax  on the ultra wealthy  which  in       was paid by only  two out of every       people,true,142,25,4.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.34,"('republicans', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')",2
Roy Blunt,our tax code has nearly doubled since,true,37,7,4.428571428571429,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,,0
Joyce Mauk,one in    babies born in this country is born in texas,true,54,11,3.727272727272727,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('texas', 'GPE')",2
Bruce Rauner,i personally am pro choice  i always have been  and i made no qualms about that when i was elected governor,true,107,21,4.0476190476190474,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.296,,0
Chris Abele,percent of americans  support universal background checks  for gun purchases,true,76,10,6.5,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0772,"('americans', 'NORP')",1
Eric Schneiderman,some states hit hardest by opioid deaths  have more opioid prescriptions than residents,true,87,13,5.6923076923076925,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,,0
Kevin Nicholson,ronald reagan was a verified democrat until his mid   s,true,55,10,4.4,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('ronald reagan', 'PERSON'), ('democrat', 'NORP')",2
Nancy Pelosi,seventy six percent of the american people support us passing the dream act   with citizenship and legalization as part of it all    more than    percent of republicans support that,true,181,29,5.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.7506,"('seventy six percent', 'PERCENT'), ('american', 'NORP'), ('republicans', 'NORP')",3
Roy Blunt,nearly     of rural missourians don t have access to broadband  that needs to change,true,84,14,4.714285714285714,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,,0
Eric Schneiderman,no court has held  deferred action for childhood arrivals  unconstitutional,true,75,10,6.4,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.296,,0
Louise Slaughter,rescinding the deferred action for childhood arrivals program  will harm our economy,true,84,12,6.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.5423,,0
Betty Jean Grant,i m the only candidate who has not accepted money from carl paladino nor lpciminelli  two of the biggest developers in the city of buffalo,true,138,25,4.52,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.2057,"('carl', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')",2
Kamala Harris,it costs us about         a year  on average nationally  to lock somebody up  in california it costs about         a year,true,121,20,4.15,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('california', 'GPE')",1
Donald Trump,says his time away from washington coincides with a  long planned renovation  for the white house,true,97,16,5.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('washington', 'GPE'), ('the white house', 'ORG')",2
Eric Schneiderman,we have been able to cut new york s uninsured rate in half since      from    percent to   percent of our population,true,116,21,4.095238095238095,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.2732,"('new york', 'GPE'), ('half', 'CARDINAL')",2
John Faso,we now have about one third of new york s population on medicaid,true,64,13,4.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('about one third', 'CARDINAL'), ('new york', 'GPE'), ('medicaid', 'ORG')",3
Joe Straus,one  texas school  district alone    austin isd    is expected to lose more than      million in local property taxes to robin hood this year,true,141,23,4.608695652173913,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.5719,"('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('texas', 'GPE'), ('austin', 'PERSON'), ('more than      million', 'MONEY'), ('this year', 'DATE')",5
Gavin Newsom,more than a million californians  do not have  clean water to bathe in or drink,true,79,15,4.2,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.3089,"('more than a million', 'CARDINAL'), ('californians', 'NORP')",2
Bobby Scott,today s minimum wage worker making       an hour has less buying power than a minimum wage worker in the     s,true,110,20,4.05,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.0,"('today', 'DATE')",1
Ralph Northam,on extreme risk guns laws   this idea has passed republican legislatures in other states and has been signed by republican governors,true,132,21,5.238095238095238,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.2732,"('republican', 'NORP'), ('republican', 'NORP')",2
Nita Lowey,the facts are  the majority of opioids and all kinds of other things that are connected to the opioids are coming through the point of entry,true,140,26,4.384615384615385,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.0,,0
Andrew Cuomo,new york has passed  the best paid family leave  program in the united states of america,true,88,16,4.4375,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.7783,"('new york', 'GPE'), ('the united states of america', 'GPE')",2
Roy Blunt,the national defense authorization act for fiscal year       includes the largest pay raise in nearly    years,true,110,16,5.375,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0258,"('the national defense authorization act', 'ORG'), ('fiscal year', 'DATE'), ('nearly    years', 'DATE')",3
Mike Romano,adjusting for inflation  west virginia s median household income has not grown in a decade,true,90,15,5.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('west virginia', 'GPE'), ('a decade', 'DATE')",2
Mike Romano,the poverty rate in west virginia  was      percent  the fourth highest in the country,true,86,14,4.714285714285714,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.5106,"('west virginia', 'GPE'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL')",2
Andrew Cuomo,there is nothing that we have done on amazon that we have not done with hundreds of other projects,true,98,19,4.2105263157894735,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.1779,"('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')",1
Mike Romano,in       west virginia s         median household income was         below the national average  ranking   th,true,109,14,5.071428571428571,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('west virginia s         ', 'LOC')",1
Bloggers,says ann coulter said   i am a settler  i am descended from settlers   not from immigrants,true,90,16,4.375,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('ann coulter', 'PERSON')",1
Richard Ojeda,at general motors  ceo mary barra  took home almost    million dollars last year alone     x your company s average employee,true,124,20,4.8,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.25,"('general motors  ceo', 'ORG'), ('mary barra', 'PERSON'), ('almost    million dollars', 'MONEY'), ('last year', 'DATE')",4
David McKinley,the united states  spends more on potato chips than we do on all energy r d,true,75,16,3.6875,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.5994,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1
Crystal Quade,missouri  had the largest amount of millennial democrats running than any other state in the country,true,100,16,5.25,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('missouri', 'GPE'), ('democrats', 'NORP')",2
Jason Smith,in fact   out of    new jobs in america are created by small businesses,true,71,13,4.153846153846154,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.25,"('america', 'GPE')",1
West Virginia Republican Party,middle class income rose to a record level in      as the strong economy lifted the fortunes of more americans,true,110,19,4.578947368421052,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.5106,"('americans', 'NORP')",1
Richard Ojeda,we have lost more lives in the last two years  due to opioids  than all of the lives lost during the vietnam war,true,112,23,3.8260869565217392,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.8176,"('the last two years', 'DATE'), ('the vietnam war', 'EVENT')",2
Patrick Morrisey,says joe manchin  refused to commit to kavanaugh until after the senate had the votes,true,85,15,4.666666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('joe manchin  ', 'PERSON'), ('senate', 'ORG')",2
Bloggers,trump supporters are heading to the border as the migrant caravan approaches,true,76,12,5.416666666666667,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.4404,,0
Nate McMurray,do you know that new york state pays out way more than they ever get back,true,73,16,3.625,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('new york', 'GPE')",1
Donald Trump,household income among hispanic americans has just set a new record high,true,72,12,5.083333333333333,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('hispanic', 'NORP'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2
Joe Manchin,west virginia  has the highest overdose rate per capita of any state in our nation,true,82,15,4.466666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('west virginia', 'GPE')",1
Jon Tester,matt rosendale supports plans that don t have to cover  pre existing conditions,true,79,13,5.076923076923077,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.3612,"('matt rosendale', 'PERSON'), ('don', 'PERSON')",2
Marc Molinaro,on spending growth under gov  andrew cuomo   despite the fact that you continue to suggest that you ve been able to hold the two percent  you haven t,true,149,28,4.214285714285714,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.3818,"('andrew cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('two percent', 'PERCENT')",2
Claire McCaskill,my opponent is endorsed by citizens united,true,42,7,5.142857142857143,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.5859,,0
Jim Justice,thousands of folks are opening west virginia e zpass accounts,true,61,10,5.2,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('west virginia', 'GPE')",2
Joe Manchin,black lung cases are at a    year high,true,38,8,3.5,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,,0
Erin Forrest,percent of the town boards in wisconsin have no women on them at all,true,68,14,3.9285714285714284,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.296,"('wisconsin', 'GPE')",1
Greta Van Susteren,says president donald trump  had a different opinion  in      than he does now about whether  barack  obama should have intervened in syria after obama s red line was crossed,true,174,29,4.724137931034483,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,0.0,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('syria', 'GPE'), ('obama s red line', 'FAC')",3
Ted Yoho,afghanistan has more hectares  of opium poppies  planted today than they had before we started this war,true,103,17,5.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.6833,"('afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')",2
Chris Collins,in new york state   you cannot charge an older person even one dollar more than a younger person  for health insurance,true,118,21,4.523809523809524,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('new york', 'GPE'), ('one dollar', 'MONEY')",2
Jerry Brown,million jobs have been created in the last six or seven years  in california,true,76,14,4.428571428571429,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.25,"('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('the last six or seven years  in', 'DATE'), ('california', 'GPE')",3
Carolyn Maloney,more than half of planned parenthood facilities are in rural or medically underserved areas,true,91,14,5.571428571428571,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('more than half', 'CARDINAL')",1
Habitat for Humanity of Broward,south florida ranks no    in the gap between wages and housing,true,62,11,4.454545454545454,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.296,"('florida', 'GPE')",1
Ron Johnson,the gop s obamacare replacement would reduce subsidies that help lower income people buy health insurance  but also  expand the entitlement  by giving subsidies to higher income people  that obamacare never helped,true,213,32,5.5625,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,0.743,"('gop', 'ORG')",1
Claire McCaskill,small businesses  create two out of every three american jobs,true,61,10,5.1,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.2732,"('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('american', 'NORP')",3
The Coalition for Public Schools,texas legislators have filed voucher proposals in every legislative session since       but all of them have failed to become law,true,129,20,5.2,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.6652,"('texas', 'GPE')",1
Donald Trump,one third of the counties   think of it  one third   only have one insurer left  on the affordable care act exchanges,true,117,21,4.333333333333333,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.4939,"('one third', 'CARDINAL'), ('one third', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",3
Donna Howard,says condoms  used to be tax exempt here in texas,true,49,10,3.9,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.1027,"('texas', 'GPE')",1
