Politician,Quote,word_count,word_length,adv_count,adj_count,noun_count,verb_count,det_count,sentiment,named_entities,named_entities_count,Truth value
5,in the u s    a person can be married in the morning and thrown out of a restaurant for being gay in the afternoon,24,3.6666666666666665,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('afternoon', 'TIME')",1,1.0
2,texas republicans just voted to give a republican appointee the power to single handedly cancel election results in the state s largest democratic county,24,5.416666666666667,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.25,"('texas', 'GPE'), ('republicans', 'NORP'), ('republican', 'NORP')",3,1.0
5,we cut black child poverty in half in      because of the child tax credit,14,4.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.4215,"('half', 'CARDINAL')",1,1.0
1,we banned transgender  people from serving in the military,9,5.444444444444445,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.4588,,0,1.0
5,studies show that children who go to preschool are nearly     more likely to finish high school and go on to earn a two  or four year degree  no matter their background they came from,34,4.235294117647059,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.2732,"('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('four year', 'DATE')",2,1.0
5,since a new immigration program was implemented  the number of venezuelans trying to enter the u s  illegally decreased  from about       per day to less than     per day on average,30,4.633333333333334,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.0772,,0,1.0
5,for the last several months  wages have gone up more than prices have gone up,15,4.133333333333334,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('the last several months', 'DATE')",1,1.0
5,says ron johnson  wants to put social security and medicare on the chopping block every single year,17,4.823529411764706,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.128,"('ron johnson', 'PERSON'), ('medicare', 'ORG'), ('every single year', 'DATE')",3,1.0
5,in        only nine nato allies were spending     of their gdp on defense   this year     will spend at least,18,4.166666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.128,"('only nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('this year', 'DATE')",2,1.0
5,if the affordable care act were terminated   that would mean over a hundred million americans will lose protections for preexisting conditions,21,5.714285714285714,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.128,"('over a hundred million', 'CARDINAL'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2,1.0
5,due to the arrangements that i ve reached with  mexico  president obrador  the number of migrants coming   to our shared border unlawfully in recent months has dropped dramatically,28,5.285714285714286,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.4767,"('mexico', 'GPE'), ('recent months', 'DATE')",2,1.0
5,starting in       no matter what your total bills are for prescription drugs   medicare part d users will never pay  more than        a year  because some of these cancer drugs are         to         bucks a year,34,4.294117647058823,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,-0.7355,"('medicare', 'ORG')",1,1.0
5,support for roe is higher today in america than it has ever been,13,4.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.4019,"('today', 'DATE'), ('america', 'GPE')",2,1.0
4,a new missouri bill  would put teachers on the sex offense registry if they  contribute to social transition   of transgender students  including by using gender affirming pronouns,27,5.518518518518518,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.25,"('missouri', 'GPE')",1,1.0
5,if you went  anywhere in the world   you could get a prescription filled for     to     less than it costs in the u s,23,3.652173913043478,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('the u s', 'ORG')",1,1.0
5,raising the debt limit is paying our old debts  it has nothing to do with new spending,17,4.0588235294117645,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.3612,,0,1.0
5,thirty years ago  the united states ranked sixth among advanced economies in the share of women in the workforce  you know where we are today  twenty three,27,4.666666666666667,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.7184,"('thirty years ago', 'DATE'), ('the united states', 'GPE'), ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('twenty three', 'CARDINAL')",5,1.0
2,ivermectin has been fda approved for human use since,9,4.888888888888889,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.4215,"('ivermectin', 'PERSON'), ('fda', 'ORG')",2,1.0
5,women are  disproportionately impacted by voter id laws   especially married women who change their names  or those whose ids do not accurately reflect their gender,25,5.44,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.0,,0,1.0
2,sailors at sea  all vaxxed  all with covid  seven  weeks following deployment,12,5.166666666666667,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('seven  weeks', 'DATE')",1,1.0
4,the man next to mike pompeo in a november      photo  is the guy the trump administration helped get out of jail in      and who is now the  president  of afghanistan,30,4.133333333333334,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,0.0,"('mike', 'PERSON'), ('november', 'DATE'), ('afghanistan', 'GPE')",3,1.0
5,when terry mcauliffe was governor   unemployment went down in every single county  including rural virginia by nearly,17,5.764705882352941,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.4404,"('virginia', 'GPE')",1,1.0
6,george washington mandated smallpox vaccines for the continental army,9,6.777777777777778,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('george washington', 'PERSON'), ('the continental army', 'ORG')",2,1.0
5,ten thousand people have recently died        of them  thereabouts  are people who hadn t been vaccinated,16,5.0625,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.5574,"('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL')",1,1.0
5,in       more people voted in america than ever in the history of america  in the middle of a once in a century pandemic,23,3.9565217391304346,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,"('america', 'GPE'), ('america', 'GPE'), ('a century', 'DATE')",3,1.0
2,the new york times published an old stock photo of a young girl and claimed israeli forces killed her during its recent war with hamas,25,4.4,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.8555,"('the new york times', 'ORG'), ('israeli', 'NORP'), ('hamas', 'ORG')",3,1.0
5,we ve created close to         manufacturing jobs since i ve taken office,12,4.5,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.25,,0,1.0
5,last year alone  natural disasters in america caused      billion in damages,11,5.454545454545454,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.7184,"('last year', 'DATE'), ('america', 'GPE')",2,1.0
5,over the past four decades  we ve lost over         farms in america  and  over     million acres of farmland  and that s an area roughly equal to the size of minnesota  north and south dakota combined,35,4.285714285714286,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.3182,"('the past four decades', 'DATE'), ('america', 'GPE'), ('over     million acres', 'QUANTITY'), ('farmland', 'GPE'), ('minnesota', 'GPE')",5,1.0
5,since joe biden  has taken office  unemployment in our  latino  community has been cut in half,16,4.6875,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.6124,"('joe biden  ', 'PERSON'), ('half', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
5,u s  inflation is  now down close to     the lowest among the world s leading economies,16,4.125,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.3818,,0,1.0
5,according to the congressional budget office   the inflation reduction act  will save the federal government      billion over the next    years because medicare will be paying less for the prescription drugs they re making available to seniors,36,5.5,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,0.4939,"('the next    years', 'DATE'), ('medicare', 'ORG')",2,1.0
5,the no    weather related killer is heat      people die annually from its effects  more than from floods  hurricanes and tornadoes in america combined,23,5.173913043478261,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.886,"('annually', 'DATE'), ('america', 'GPE')",2,1.0
2,an  anti black lives matter  flag replaced the american flag behind president trump during a waukesha campaign rally,18,5.388888888888889,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.296,"('american', 'NORP'), ('waukesha', 'GPE')",2,1.0
5,after the american rescue plan s food and nutrition assistance   hunger is already sharply down in the united states,19,5.052631578947368,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.6249,"('american', 'NORP'), ('the united states', 'GPE')",2,1.0
5,a new  independent study put out last week found that at least    of our largest corporations used various loopholes to pay zero federal income tax in,26,4.653846153846154,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.1027,"('last week', 'DATE'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
6,says sen  cory booker wants to require a federal license for gun owners but criticizes voter id laws as discriminatory,20,4.9,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.5859,,0,1.0
6,these    mass shootings involved an ar    style weapon,8,5.125,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.296,,0,1.0
2,in aberdeen  miss    massive     of mail in ballots proved fraudulent  judge orders election do over,15,5.133333333333334,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.5859,,0,1.0
2,says al gore said in      that  the north pole will be ice free in the summer by      because of man made global warming,23,3.782608695652174,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.5994,"('al gore', 'PERSON'), ('the summer', 'DATE')",2,1.0
6,covid    infections down     from trump s last day  covid    vaccinations up     from trump s last day  competence matters,18,4.944444444444445,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0258,"('last day', 'DATE'), ('last day', 'DATE')",2,1.0
2,omicron is  the fastest spreading virus known to humankind,9,5.444444444444445,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('omicron', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
2,a white armed robbery suspect was sentenced to two years in jail while a black armed robbery suspect was sentenced to    years in prison by the same florida judge,29,4.517241379310345,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,-0.7845,"('two years', 'DATE'), ('florida', 'GPE')",2,1.0
5,says president donald trump  took more than a month to allocate congress  emergency funding to tribes   and only did so after tribes sued,23,4.826086956521739,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.3818,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('more than a month', 'DATE'), ('congress', 'ORG')",3,1.0
2,hidden in the cares act was an obscure      billion tax break for        millionaires,13,4.6923076923076925,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.4588,,0,1.0
1,under three years of my administration  net farm income has already gone up nearly,14,4.857142857142857,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('under three years', 'DATE')",1,1.0
6,a long list shows  new cdc guidelines for reopening schools,10,4.9,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('cdc', 'ORG')",1,1.0
2,pelosi s new coronavirus bill allows illegals to receive billions in relief funds in past  current  and future payments,19,5.2105263157894735,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.4767,"('pelosi s new', 'PERSON'), ('billions', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
2,retail  milk has gone up      since this time last year  the price farmers are paid has dropped,17,4.235294117647059,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('last year', 'DATE')",1,1.0
2,covid    is  here to stay  and  we need to accept that and be prepared to deal with covid long term,20,3.7,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.5423,,0,1.0
6,says a california surfer was  alone  in the ocean   when he was arrested for violating the state s stay at home order,22,4.181818181818182,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.8225,"('california', 'GPE')",1,1.0
2,says a study projects wisconsin s coronavirus cases will peak on april,12,4.916666666666667,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('wisconsin s coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('april', 'DATE')",2,1.0
2,says truck drivers are being turned away from fast food restaurants during the covid    pandemic,15,5.266666666666667,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,,0,1.0
2,bill gates told us about the coronavirus in,8,4.5,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,"('bill gates', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
1,says nancy pelosi s coronavirus bill includes  tax credits for solar and wind energy   retirement plans for community newspaper employees        million for pbs   climate change studies  and more,28,5.535714285714286,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,0.5574,"('nancy pelosi s coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('pbs', 'ORG')",2,1.0
2,wisconsin is the only state where all republicans voted against protecting its citizens,13,5.769230769230769,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('wisconsin', 'ORG'), ('republicans', 'NORP')",2,1.0
2,coronavirus can live for  up to   hours in the air  up to   hours on copper  up to    hours on cardboard up to   days on plastic and stainless steel,28,3.892857142857143,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('days', 'DATE')",1,1.0
2,says        blacks didn t vote in milwaukee  in,8,4.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('milwaukee', 'GPE')",1,1.0
6,says     of novel coronavirus cases are  mild,7,4.857142857142857,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.3182,,0,1.0
2,says joe biden  attacked voters this primary   saying  damn liar    full of s     and  dog faced pony soldier,18,4.444444444444445,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.8402,"('joe biden', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
2,federal law requires people to speak english to be naturalized as american citizens,13,5.461538461538462,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('english', 'LANGUAGE'), ('american', 'NORP')",2,1.0
5,all the billionaires in america  their net worth combined   has increased by      billion  during the pandemic,16,5.375,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.4588,"('america', 'GPE')",1,1.0
5,if you just count all the deaths in the red states  we are number two in the world in deaths  just behind brazil,23,3.8260869565217392,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0772,"('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('brazil', 'GPE')",2,1.0
6,in       joe biden paid            in federal income taxes and kamala harris paid          while donald trump paid,16,4.5625,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('joe biden', 'PERSON'), ('kamala harris', 'PERSON'), ('donald trump', 'PERSON')",3,1.0
5,says amy coney barrett  has a written track record  disagreeing adamantly with the supreme court s decision to uphold the aca  in fact  she publicly criticized chief justice roberts  opinion upholding the law eight years ago,36,5.111111111111111,31.0,31.0,31.0,31.0,31.0,0.4767,"('coney barrett', 'PERSON'), ('the supreme court', 'ORG'), ('roberts', 'PERSON'), ('the law eight years ago', 'DATE')",4,1.0
2,says donald trump funded a veterans day parade    years ago in new york city after the city refused to pay,20,4.2,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.3818,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('day', 'DATE'), ('new york city', 'GPE')",3,1.0
5,more cops have died from covid this year than have been killed on patrol,14,4.214285714285714,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.8542,"('this year', 'DATE')",1,1.0
5,i am not banning fracking,5,4.2,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,,0,1.0
4,a texas gop lawmaker recently introduced a bill that would allow the death penalty for women who have an abortion,20,4.7,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.7184,"('texas', 'GPE'), ('gop', 'ORG')",2,1.0
5,the supreme court decision overturning roe v  wade  made the united states an outlier among developed nations in the world  on abortion rights,23,5.086956521739131,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.7506,"('supreme court', 'ORG'), ('the united states', 'GPE')",2,1.0
2,more people die from hands  fists  feet  than rifles,9,4.555555555555555,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.6344,,0,1.0
2,florida highway patrol has a semi truck   the fhp uses a fleet of three such  hidden in plain sight  trucks to snitch on bad drivers,25,4.16,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.5423,"('florida', 'GPE'), ('fhp', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')",3,1.0
5,when we passed the assault weapons ban  mass shootings went down  when the law expired  mass shootings tripled,18,5.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.8834,,0,1.0
2,the red cross sells your donated blood to hospitals for      and then that hospital charges you thousands for a blood transfusion,21,4.9523809523809526,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.2732,"('the red cross', 'ORG'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
5,make no mistake  the current spike in gas prices is largely the fault of vladimir putin,16,4.4375,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.743,"('putin', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
2,u s  imports    of its oil from russia while  exxon  chevron  bp and shell profits are at their highest level in over   years,23,4.086956521739131,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.4404,"('russia', 'GPE'), ('exxon', 'ORG'), ('chevron', 'ORG'), ('over   years', 'DATE')",4,1.0
5,the oil industry has        permits to drill now  they could be drilling right now  yesterday  last week  last year,19,4.526315789473684,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('yesterday', 'DATE'), ('last week  last year', 'DATE')",2,1.0
5,asked about asylum seekers in camps in mexico   this is the first time ever you ve had to seek asylum in a third country,24,3.9583333333333335,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.0,"('mexico', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')",3,1.0
5,if the vaccine came out tomorrow  how in the heck would we get it to people  there is no game plan,21,3.619047619047619,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.296,"('tomorrow', 'DATE')",1,1.0
6,photos show six fires around the world  in the last    hours,11,4.181818181818182,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('the last    hours', 'TIME')",2,1.0
5,i  all the way back in january  warned  president trump that  this pandemic was coming  i talked about what we needed to do,23,4.173913043478261,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.2732,"('january', 'DATE')",1,1.0
2,says joe biden has said     million americans died from guns and another     million from covid,15,4.866666666666666,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.5574,"('joe biden', 'PERSON'), ('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('americans', 'NORP')",3,1.0
2,says a leader of the blackfeet nation tribe designed the current washington redskins logo and once said it  made us all proud to have an indian on a big time team,31,4.225806451612903,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,0.4767,"('washington', 'GPE'), ('indian', 'NORP')",2,1.0
2,new zealand let health experts  rather than politicians make decisions about how to deal with covid      and as of today they have zero covid cases,25,4.68,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('new zealand', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL')",3,1.0
5,three hundred sixty thousand pennsylvanians fought on the side of the union to defeat the flag  that confederate flag  including more black soldiers coming from pennsylvania than any other state in the nation,33,5.2727272727272725,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,-0.6486,"('three hundred sixty thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('pennsylvania', 'GPE')",2,1.0
5,the cdc tried to develop clear guidelines about what the stages of re opening should look like   the administration delayed and scaled them back,24,4.958333333333333,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.4939,"('cdc', 'ORG')",1,1.0
5,trump lost a trade war that he started,8,3.875,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.7351,,0,1.0
1,as of june     the covid    death rate is  way down,10,3.4,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.5994,"('june', 'DATE')",1,1.0
2,trump s daughter works at the white house  her husband works at the white house  rudy s son works at the white house  barr s son in law works at the white house  barr s daughter works at treasury  trump s sons do foreign business  trump s daughter is getting chinese patents and saudi grants,55,4.2,47.0,47.0,47.0,47.0,47.0,0.4019,"('trump s daughter', 'PERSON'), ('the white house', 'ORG'), ('the white house  rudy s son', 'ORG'), ('the white house', 'ORG'), ('barr s son', 'PERSON'), ('the white house', 'ORG'), ('barr s daughter', 'PERSON'), ('treasury', 'ORG'), ('chinese', 'NORP'), ('saudi', 'NORP')",10,1.0
1,very close to     million people are now working in the united states  nobody s ever even come close to that number,21,4.285714285714286,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.4767,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1,1.0
1,says iranian gen  qassem soleimani  was a designated terrorist by president obama  who didn t do anything about it,19,4.894736842105263,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.6908,"('iranian gen  qassem', 'PERSON'), ('obama', 'PERSON')",2,1.0
5,you have to have congressional authority  to close guantanamo bay prison,11,5.545454545454546,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.4588,"('guantanamo bay', 'LOC')",1,1.0
1,president trump has lifted the prospect of voters across vermont  overseeing a        decline of vermont residents on food stamps,19,5.421052631578948,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.296,"('vermont', 'GPE'), ('vermont', 'GPE')",2,1.0
5,i entered as one of the poorest men in congress  left one of the poorest men in government  in congress and as vice president,24,4.166666666666667,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.7906,"('congress', 'ORG'), ('congress', 'ORG')",2,1.0
5,we re no longer the wealthiest middle class in the world,11,4.181818181818182,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.25,,0,1.0
1,last year  we prosecuted a record number of firearms offenses,10,5.1,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.5859,"('last year', 'DATE')",1,1.0
5,says kamala harris oversaw a police department that was  abusing people s rights  and that she did not  disclose to defense attorneys  when there was exculpatory evidence   she didn t do that  she never did it  and so  what happened  along came a federal judge and said enough  enough  and he freed       of these people,55,4.509090909090909,38.0,38.0,38.0,38.0,38.0,-0.1705,"('kamala harris', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
5,we made parity between mental health and physical health  it was a fundamental breakthrough in how we thought about how things should work,23,5.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,,0,1.0
1,says cory booker has accepted over          from the pharmaceutical industry during his political career,14,5.857142857142857,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.2732,"('cory booker', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
5,in the obama biden administration  we got china to cut cyber theft    it s gotten significantly worse under this administration,20,5.2,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.6369,"('china', 'GPE')",1,1.0
0,americans  would run out of avocados in three weeks  if imports from mexico were stopped due to a border closure,20,4.55,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.2263,"('americans', 'NORP'), ('three weeks', 'DATE'), ('mexico', 'GPE')",3,1.0
0,in february alone there were enough illegal immigrants who crossed the border to fill this  kansas city chiefs  arrowhead  stadium,20,5.4,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.6808,"('february', 'DATE'), ('kansas', 'GPE')",2,1.0
5,the current school psychologist to student ratio in this country is roughly       to    while experts say it should be at most     to,22,4.5,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,,0,1.0
1,only     of legal immigrants are selected based on skill or based on merit  in countries like canada  australia and new zealand  and others  that number is closer to     and even    and     in some cases,34,4.441176470588236,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,0.7269,"('canada', 'GPE'), ('australia', 'GPE'), ('new zealand', 'GPE')",3,1.0
1,when abraham lincoln made the gettysburg address speech  the great speech  do you know he was ridiculed  he was ridiculed,20,4.95,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0258,"('abraham lincoln', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
2,facebook video purports to show man flying a hoverboard at over     miles per hour,14,4.642857142857143,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0,1.0
0,say a  left wing extremist  chases down  rams car over trump bumper sticker,13,4.615384615384615,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,,0,1.0
0,says donald trump contradicted his own administration when he said the decision to allow blueprints for  d printed guns to be distributed  doesn t seem to make much sense,29,4.827586206896552,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,-0.1027,"('donald trump', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
1,there s been a       percent increase in asylum claims over the last    years,13,4.307692307692308,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.3182,"('the last    years', 'DATE')",1,1.0
1,canada charges the u s  a      tariff on dairy products  they didn t tell you that  did they  not fair to our farmers,23,3.739130434782609,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.47,"('canada', 'GPE')",1,1.0
1,utilities cut rates  credit gop tax cuts,7,4.714285714285714,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.1779,"('gop', 'ORG')",1,1.0
0,national guard storms mexico border  makes game changing impact in just    days,12,5.333333333333333,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('national guard', 'ORG'), ('mexico', 'GPE'), ('just    days', 'DATE')",3,1.0
1,says sen  richard blumenthal  lied about his service  in vietnam,10,5.2,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.3818,"('richard blumenthal', 'PERSON'), ('vietnam', 'GPE')",2,1.0
1,since nafta s adoption  the united states racked up trade deficits totaling more than    trillion,15,5.266666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.4215,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1,1.0
1,under the north american free trade agreement   we lost thousands of plants,12,5.166666666666667,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.6369,"('north american', 'NORP'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
0,hillary on child aliens in       send them back,8,4.25,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,0.0,"('hillary', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
0,migrants demand         each to go home  or else,8,4.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.128,,0,1.0
0,border patrol agents were caught on film destroying supplies left to help migrants,13,5.384615384615385,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.2263,,0,1.0
0,principal bans candy canes,4,5.75,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,0.0,,0,1.0
0,says clint eastwood said  one day we will realize that the barack obama presidency was the biggest fraud ever perpetrated on the american people,24,5.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.5859,"('clint eastwood', 'PERSON'), ('one day', 'DATE'), ('american', 'NORP')",3,1.0
1,coal production up      in past year  down       last    years   endingwaroncoal,10,5.4,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('past year', 'DATE'), ('last    years', 'DATE')",2,1.0
1,the nfl is  getting massive tax breaks,7,4.428571428571429,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('nfl', 'ORG')",1,1.0
0,say sean hannity said in      that obama s willingness to meet with north korea was  disturbing  while trump s  willingness to meet with north korea is a huge foreign policy win,31,4.483870967741935,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,0.7184,"('sean', 'NORP'), ('north korea', 'GPE'), ('north korea', 'GPE')",3,1.0
1,says the u s  steel and aluminum industry is  a fraction of what it once was,16,3.6875,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,,0,1.0
1,rep  dan donovan  voted for tax cuts,7,4.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.296,"('rep  dan donovan', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
1,in       an officer was assaulted in america on an average of every    minutes,13,4.384615384615385,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.5267,"('america', 'GPE'), ('every    minutes', 'TIME')",2,1.0
1,kanye  west  looks and he sees black unemployment at the lowest it s been in the history of our country  he sees hispanic unemployment at the lowest it s been in the history of our country  he sees  women s unemployment  the lowest it s been in now almost    years,50,4.12,34.0,34.0,34.0,34.0,34.0,-0.9382,"('kanye', 'GPE'), ('hispanic', 'NORP'), ('almost    years', 'DATE')",3,1.0
1,when a car is sent to the united states from china  there is a tariff to be paid of         when a car is sent to china from the united states  there is a tariff to be paid of,38,3.3684210526315788,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,0.6808,"('the united states', 'GPE'), ('china', 'GPE'), ('china', 'GPE'), ('the united states', 'GPE')",4,1.0
1,for the first time in the modern political era  we have confirmed a new justice in the first     days,19,4.105263157894737,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.5267,"('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the first     days', 'DATE')",2,1.0
1,since china joined   that s another beauty   the wto in       the u s  has lost many more than        factories,19,3.947368421052632,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.3612,"('china', 'GPE'), ('the u s  ', 'ORG')",2,1.0
1,in the first full month of my administration following the issuance of my executive orders  illegal immigration on our southern border fell by an unprecedented    percent,26,5.423076923076923,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.5574,"('the first full month', 'DATE')",1,1.0
1,the stock market has hit record numbers  as you know  and there has been a tremendous surge of optimism in the business world,23,4.391304347826087,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.5423,,0,1.0
1,says      of refugees admitted into u s              during court breakdown are from   countries  syria  iraq  somalia  iran  sudan  libya   yemen,20,4.95,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.1027,"('syria', 'GPE'), ('iraq', 'GPE'), ('somalia', 'GPE'), ('iran', 'GPE'), ('sudan', 'GPE'), ('libya', 'GPE'), ('yemen', 'GPE')",7,1.0
0,more than two thirds of the aliens the obama administration has brought to the united states under the president s central american minors program weren t actually minors at all,30,4.933333333333334,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,0.4215,"('more than two thirds', 'CARDINAL'), ('the united states', 'GPE'), ('american', 'NORP')",3,1.0
1,nearly one in four people in their prime working years are not working,13,4.461538461538462,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('four', 'CARDINAL')",1,1.0
1,says nevadans will have a  double digit hike in their obamacare premiums for the year  and     of nevada s    counties will only have one obamacare   exchange insurer,27,4.777777777777778,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.0,"('the year', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
3,says donald trump is  the first person running for president  republican or democrat  who refused to say that he would respect the results of this election,26,4.884615384615385,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.2263,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('republican', 'NORP'), ('democrat', 'NORP')",4,1.0
1,so now they take drugs  literally  and they throw it  a hundred pounds of drugs  they throw it over the wall  they have catapults  but they throw it over the wall  and it lands and it hits somebody on the head,41,3.951219512195122,23.0,23.0,23.0,23.0,23.0,0.0,"('a hundred pounds', 'QUANTITY')",1,1.0
1,since we passed tax cuts  over   million workers have gotten tax cut bonuses   many of them thousands and thousands of dollars,21,4.809523809523809,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0772,"('thousands and thousands', 'CARDINAL')",1,1.0
1,we admit about         permanent immigrants from the middle east every year,11,5.181818181818182,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.2023,"('the middle east', 'LOC')",1,1.0
1,russia and china are  doing naval exercises together someplace,9,5.888888888888889,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('russia', 'GPE'), ('china', 'GPE')",2,1.0
1,american homeownership rate in q       was         lowest rate in   yrs,10,4.6,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.3818,"('american homeownership', 'ORG')",1,1.0
3,says trump ties are made  in china  not colorado  trump suits in mexico  not michigan  trump furniture in turkey  not ohio  trump picture frames in india  not wisconsin,28,4.75,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,0.0,"('china', 'GPE'), ('colorado', 'GPE'), ('mexico', 'GPE'), ('turkey', 'GPE'), ('ohio', 'GPE'), ('india', 'GPE')",6,1.0
1,our navy has shrunk from more than     ships in      to     in,11,3.5454545454545454,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,"('navy', 'ORG')",1,1.0
1,the russians  tried to hack the republican national committee  and they were unable to break through,16,5.1875,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('russians', 'NORP'), ('the republican national committee', 'ORG')",2,1.0
1,america s federal business tax rate is the highest  in the world,12,4.333333333333333,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('america s federal business tax rate', 'ORG')",1,1.0
3,immigrants start businesses at a faster rate  they seem to grow those businesses more successfully,15,5.533333333333333,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.5413,,0,1.0
1,says he and bernie sanders have  very similar  views on trade,11,4.454545454545454,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('bernie', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
1,nearly         illegal immigrants with criminal records  ordered deported from our country  are tonight roaming free to threaten peaceful citizens,19,6.2105263157894735,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.4767,"('tonight', 'TIME')",1,1.0
1,household incomes are down more than        since the year,9,4.777777777777778,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('the year', 'DATE')",1,1.0
1,while hillary clinton plans a massive  and i mean massive  tax increase  i have proposed the largest tax reduction of any candidate who has run for president this year  democrat or republican,32,4.875,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,0.3182,"('hillary clinton', 'PERSON'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('democrat', 'NORP'), ('republican', 'NORP')",4,1.0
1,taxpayers are paying a fortune for the use of air force one on the campaign trail  by president barack obama and hillary clinton,23,4.565217391304348,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.0,"('hillary clinton', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
3,after britain s vote to leave the european union   within    hours  americans lost      billion from our     k s,18,4.444444444444445,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.3612,"('britain', 'GPE'), ('the european union', 'ORG'), ('americans', 'NORP')",3,1.0
3,we just had the best year for the auto industry in america in history,14,4.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.6369,"('the best year', 'DATE'), ('america', 'GPE')",2,1.0
3,the market is making this decision  the market has driven down the cost of coal  so you have companies going bankrupt,21,4.523809523809524,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.5574,,0,1.0
5,cervical cancer in africa is  fully preventable with basic education  screening and vaccines,13,6.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.6597,"('africa', 'LOC')",1,1.0
3,says donald trump  said as recently as a few weeks ago in phoenix that every undocumented person would be subject to deportation,22,4.818181818181818,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.0,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('a few weeks ago', 'DATE'), ('phoenix', 'GPE')",3,1.0
3,we have        people a year who die from guns,9,3.4444444444444446,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.5994,,0,1.0
1,says hillary clinton  promised  running for the senate years ago          jobs for upstate new york      not only didn t they come  but they lost so many jobs,27,4.25925925925926,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.296,"('hillary clinton', 'PERSON'), ('years ago', 'DATE')",2,1.0
1,these people that we were going to deport for good reason ended up becoming citizens  ended up becoming citizens  and it was      and now it turns out it might be        and they don t even know,36,4.027777777777778,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,0.4404,,0,1.0
3,says donald trump  was one of the people who rooted for the housing crisis  he said back in        gee  i hope it does collapse because then i can go in and buy some and make some money,37,3.756756756756757,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,-0.6597,"('donald trump', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
1,ted cruz is mathematically out of winning the race,9,4.666666666666667,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.5267,,0,1.0
3,it s actually easier for the united states to get flight manifests from e u  nations than it is for e u  nations to get them from their own neighbors  thanks to an agreement the u s  negotiated when i was secretary of state,44,4.0,30.0,30.0,30.0,30.0,30.0,0.8934,"('the united states', 'GPE'), ('state', 'ORG')",2,1.0
3,we have a higher rate of tested lead in people in cleveland than in flint,15,3.933333333333333,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('cleveland', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,president obama took more money from wall street in the      campaign than anybody ever had,15,4.8,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('obama', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
1,marco rubio  has the no    absentee record in the united states  senate,12,4.583333333333333,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.128,"('marco rubio  ', 'PERSON'), ('the united states', 'GPE'), ('senate', 'ORG')",3,1.0
1,in new hampshire  i spent    million  jeb bush spent     million  he came in five  and i came in number one,20,3.85,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0772,"('new hampshire', 'GPE'), ('jeb bush', 'PERSON'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('number one', 'CARDINAL')",4,1.0
3,says dontre hamilton  who was killed during a confrontation with a milwaukee police officer  was  unarmed,16,5.4375,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.7783,"('dontre hamilton', 'PERSON'), ('milwaukee', 'GPE')",2,1.0
3,says hillary clinton won  health care for   million children,9,5.444444444444445,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.7845,"('hillary clinton', 'PERSON'), ('million', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
3,americans haven t had a raise in    years,8,3.875,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('americans', 'NORP')",1,1.0
1,according to pew research     percent of the people in afghanistan support oppressive sharia law,14,5.642857142857143,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('sharia', 'WORK_OF_ART')",2,1.0
1,says hillary clinton  plans to massively increase admissions  of middle east refugees    including a     percent increase in syrian refugees coming into our country,23,5.782608695652174,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.5574,"('hillary clinton', 'PERSON'), ('middle east', 'LOC'), ('syrian', 'NORP')",3,1.0
3,florida doesn t regulate assault weapons or     caliber rifles or large capacity ammunition magazines  it doesn t require a permit to purchase a gun  it doesn t require any registration  whatsoever,31,5.161290322580645,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,-0.8442,"('florida', 'GPE')",1,1.0
1,we admit more than         lifetime migrants from the middle east each year,12,4.666666666666667,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.2023,"('the middle east', 'LOC')",1,1.0
3,says donald trump said the u s  should  encourage  japan to get nuclear weapons,14,4.5,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.1027,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('japan', 'GPE')",2,1.0
3,in       donald trump was hoping for a real estate crash,10,4.1,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0258,,0,1.0
3,says bernie sanders  voted for regime change with respect to libya,11,5.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.4767,"('bernie sanders  ', 'PERSON'), ('libya', 'GPE')",2,1.0
3,the charleston  s c   shooter  should have never been given a gun  but the universal background check was not fast enough,21,4.571428571428571,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.1326,"('charleston', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,i spent    months putting together the sanctions against iran so that we could force them to the negotiating table,19,4.894736842105263,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('iran', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,women fill two thirds of minimum wage jobs,8,4.375,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('two thirds', 'CARDINAL')",1,1.0
3,says john kerry  is the first secretary of state to rely primarily on a government account,16,4.625,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('john kerry', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')",2,1.0
3,there have been seven investigations  of benghazi  led mostly by republicans in the congress  that concluded  nobody did anything wrong  but there were changes we could make,27,5.25925925925926,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.2617,"('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('republicans', 'NORP'), ('congress', 'ORG')",3,1.0
3,while    percent of  firearms  dealers that were inspected in      were noncompliant with federal law  only      percent of inspected dealers had their licenses revoked,23,5.652173913043479,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('only      percent', 'PERCENT')",1,1.0
6,number of americans killed by terrorism in the last decade      number of americans killed by guns in the last decade,20,4.65,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.9325,"('americans', 'NORP'), ('the last decade', 'DATE'), ('americans', 'NORP'), ('the last decade', 'DATE')",4,1.0
3,under republicans  recessions happen four times as frequently as under democrats,11,6.2727272727272725,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('republicans', 'NORP'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('democrats', 'NORP')",3,1.0
1,when carly fiorina says hewlett packard  revenues went up  that s because she bought compaq  it was a terrible deal,20,4.65,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.4767,"('hewlett packard', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
1,says marco rubio has  the worst voting record there is today,11,4.454545454545454,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.6249,"('marco rubio', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE')",2,1.0
3,twenty three million americans suffer from addiction  but only   in    get treatment,12,5.583333333333333,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.3071,"('twenty three million', 'CARDINAL'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2,1.0
6,bernie sanders opposes the death penalty  and hillary clinton supports it,11,5.636363636363637,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.6597,"('bernie sanders', 'PERSON'), ('hillary clinton', 'PERSON')",2,1.0
3,arizona schools rank   th in the nation  dead last in funding per student,13,4.461538461538462,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.6486,"('arizona', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,americans haven t had a raise in    years,8,3.875,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('americans', 'NORP')",1,1.0
3,we bailed out  johnson controls when  we saved the auto industry  and  now they want to avoid paying taxes,19,4.421052631578948,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.2263,"('johnson', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
3,there really isn t any kind of foreign policy network that is supporting and advising sen  sanders,17,4.764705882352941,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.4404,,0,1.0
3,says bernie sanders advocated putting  iranian troops into syria to try and resolve the conflict there  putting them right on the doorstep of israel,24,5.125,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.0772,"('bernie sanders', 'PERSON'), ('iranian', 'NORP'), ('syria', 'GPE'), ('israel', 'GPE')",4,1.0
3,says bernie sanders  voted for what we call the  charleston loophole,11,5.090909090909091,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('bernie sanders  ', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
3,in florida  when jeb bush was governor  state authorities conducted a deeply flawed purge of voters before the presidential election in       and  in      a plan to purge even more voters was headed off,33,4.727272727272728,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,24.0,0.0,"('florida', 'GPE'), ('jeb bush', 'PERSON')",2,1.0
3,former gov  rick perry signed a law that a federal court said was actually written with the purpose of discriminating against minority voters,23,5.130434782608695,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.0,"('rick perry', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
3,in new jersey  gov  christie vetoed legislation to extend early voting,11,5.2727272727272725,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.1779,"('new jersey', 'GPE')",1,1.0
1,within just a few years  immigration as a share of national population is set to break all historical records,19,4.7368421052631575,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.296,"('just a few years  immigration', 'DATE')",1,1.0
3,you ve got a medical report on me that meets the same standard as mitt romney and barack obama,19,4.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('mitt romney', 'PERSON')",1,1.0
1,says u s  mexico border has    million legal border crossings each and every day,14,4.5,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.128,"('mexico', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,classified material has a header which says  top secret  secret  confidential   nothing  and i will repeat this and this is verified in the report by the department of justice  none of the emails sent or received by me had such a header,42,4.476190476190476,31.0,31.0,31.0,31.0,31.0,0.6369,"('the department of justice', 'ORG')",1,1.0
1,there are at least    countries that refuse to take their people back after they ve been ordered to leave the united states  including large numbers of violent criminals,28,4.928571428571429,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.802,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,parents and teachers are already worrying about what they call the  trump effect   they report that bullying and harassment are on the rise in our schools  especially targeting students of color  muslims and immigrants,34,5.294117647058823,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,-0.8689,"('muslims', 'NORP')",1,1.0
3,says jeb bush  doesn t believe in a path to citizenship  if he did at one time  he no longer does,21,3.523809523809524,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.296,"('jeb bush', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
2,says hillary clinton s top    donors are mainly  banks  corporations and media   while bernie sanders  top    donors are labor unions,20,5.15,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.3818,"('hillary clinton', 'PERSON'), ('bernie sanders  ', 'PERSON')",2,1.0
3,american schools are  more segregated than they were in the     s,11,4.545454545454546,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('american', 'NORP')",1,1.0
3,the united states invented the community college  nobody else had ever done anything like it,15,5.133333333333334,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.6486,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,the stock market does better when you have a democratic president in the white house,15,4.666666666666667,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.4404,"('democratic', 'NORP'), ('the white house', 'ORG')",2,1.0
3,sen  rubio s  tax plan  would cut taxes for households making around    million a year by almost           which is way more than three times the earnings of a typical family,30,4.3,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.2732,"('rubio s  ', 'PERSON'), ('more than three', 'CARDINAL')",2,1.0
2,says the      republican party platform supported equal pay  the minimum wage  asylum for refugees  protections for unions and more,19,5.526315789473684,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.5574,,0,1.0
1,much more than    percent of parents out there are spankers,10,4.7,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,,0,1.0
2,in       a student who worked a minimum wage summer job could afford to pay a year s full tuition at the   year public university of their choice,27,4.111111111111111,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.1027,"('summer', 'DATE'), ('the   year', 'DATE')",2,1.0
2,percent of the     poorest counties in america are in red states,11,4.545454545454546,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.5423,"('america', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,a small majority of americans don t think they like the affordable care act  but a large majority of americans don t want to do away with the protections that are in the affordable care act,36,4.25,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,0.8225,"('americans', 'NORP'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2,1.0
3,by       the american people were overwhelmingly against the iraq war,10,5.4,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.6597,"('american', 'NORP'), ('the iraq war', 'EVENT')",2,1.0
3,in iran in       the extremists hijacked the broad based popular revolution against the shah and established a brutal theocracy,19,5.421052631578948,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.3182,"('iran', 'GPE')",1,1.0
3,canadian middle class incomes are now higher than in the united states  they are working fewer hours for more pay    living longer on average  and facing less income inequality,29,4.931034482758621,23.0,23.0,23.0,23.0,23.0,0.2748,"('canadian', 'NORP'), ('the united states', 'GPE'), ('fewer hours', 'TIME')",3,1.0
2,the cost of the food stamp program is at an all time high,13,3.4615384615384617,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,,0,1.0
2,medicare part d  was far more expensive than the affordable care act and unlike  the act   was never budgeted,19,4.578947368421052,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.4939,"('medicare', 'ORG')",1,1.0
0,forty aides who serve president barack obama  owe          in back taxes,11,4.727272727272728,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('obama', 'GPE')",1,1.0
5,the trump administration handed out taxpayer dollars to a foreign company  hundreds of homes and farms were bulldozed  and over      million in taxpayer dollars were wasted preparing for foxconn,29,5.482758620689655,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.4939,"('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')",1,2.0
1,the trump administration  achieved the lowest african american unemployment rate and the lowest african american poverty rate ever recorded,19,6.315789473684211,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,-0.886,"('african', 'NORP'), ('american', 'NORP'), ('african', 'NORP'), ('american', 'NORP')",4,2.0
5,the last administration oversaw the largest increase in murders ever recorded,11,6.090909090909091,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.4019,,0,2.0
5,wage increases have exceeded  the cost of inflation,8,5.375,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,,0,2.0
5,donald trump wants to terminate the affordable care act,9,5.222222222222222,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.4939,"('donald trump', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
1,robert f  kennedy jr  called voter id  racist   calls nra a  terrorist organization  and supports affirmative action,17,5.470588235294118,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.802,"('robert f  kennedy jr  called', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,dollar tree  walgreens  macy s  foot locker  gap  burger king  regal cinemas and kroger have had mass store closures during joe biden s presidency,24,4.875,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,0.0,"('foot locker', 'PERSON'), ('joe biden s presidency', 'PERSON')",2,2.0
5,insulin for medicare beneficiaries  was costing     bucks a month on average  it now costs     a month,16,4.8125,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.4215,"('medicare', 'ORG'), ('a month', 'DATE'), ('a month', 'DATE')",3,2.0
2,emergency officials warn to  stock up on food  water  and fuel ahead of the eclipse,15,4.4,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.4588,,0,2.0
5,the trump administration  added more to the national debt than any presidential term in american history,16,5.5,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.3612,"('american', 'NORP')",1,2.0
5,we cut the federal deficit by      billion because medicare will no longer have to pay those exorbitant prices to big pharma,21,4.714285714285714,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.7506,"('medicare', 'ORG')",1,2.0
5,we ve already cut the federal deficit by over    trillion,10,4.5,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.5859,,0,2.0
5,inflation has been at the pre pandemic level of    over the last half year,14,4.142857142857143,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('the last half year', 'DATE')",1,2.0
5,tens of thousands of auto jobs were lost nationwide during trump s presidency   but during biden s presidency   we ve created more than         auto jobs,25,4.68,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.2144,"('tens of thousands', 'CARDINAL')",1,2.0
1,the trump administration  built nearly     miles of border wall,9,5.555555555555555,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('nearly     miles', 'QUANTITY')",1,2.0
5,wages are up after being adjusted for inflation,8,5.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,,0,2.0
5,twenty six out of every     students  in k    speak spanish,10,4.2,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('twenty six', 'CARDINAL'), ('spanish', 'NORP')",2,2.0
6,canada has only  had    school shooting deaths   in history,9,5.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('canada', 'GPE')",1,2.0
5,we created more new jobs in two years than any president did in their entire term,16,4.125,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.25,"('two years', 'DATE')",1,2.0
5,two years ago this week     million people were out of work needing unemployment benefits  today  that number is under     million  the lowest in decades,24,4.958333333333333,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.3818,"('two years ago this week', 'DATE'), ('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('decades', 'DATE')",4,2.0
5,one quarter  of today s       trillion federal debt  was accumulated in the four years of my predecessor   donald trump,19,4.789473684210527,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.3612,"('one quarter', 'DATE'), ('the four years', 'DATE'), ('donald trump', 'PERSON')",3,2.0
5,take home pay for workers is going up,8,3.75,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,-0.1027,,0,2.0
4,pennsylvania drop boxes were  pre loaded  with ballots,8,5.625,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.2732,"('pennsylvania', 'GPE')",1,2.0
4,a phoenix tv station aired the election results more than a week early,13,4.461538461538462,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('more than a week early', 'DATE')",1,2.0
5,the racial wealth gap is the smallest it s been in    years,12,3.75,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.4939,,0,2.0
1,nikki haley  says the retirement age at    is way too low  it must be much higher,16,3.8125,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.2732,"('nikki haley', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
5,republicans in congress are  trying to wipe out federal funding to end the hiv epidemic,15,4.8,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('republicans', 'NORP'), ('congress', 'ORG')",2,2.0
1,when i came into office  iran had     billion in foreign exchange reserves    by the time i left  they had nothing  they were broke,23,4.304347826086956,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.3252,"('iran', 'GPE')",1,2.0
4,u s  aid to ukraine will continue during a government shutdown  but programs for food stamps  transportation  education  justice  environmental protection and homelessness will not,25,6.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.6808,"('ukraine', 'GPE')",1,2.0
5,i taught at the university of pennsylvania for four years,10,4.8,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('the university of pennsylvania', 'ORG'), ('four years', 'DATE')",2,2.0
4,boston university creates a new covid strain that has an     kill rate,12,4.583333333333333,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.5859,"('boston university', 'ORG')",1,2.0
5,this year  it s going to be over      trillion  that we ve  reduced the debt,15,3.6,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.3612,"('this year', 'DATE')",1,2.0
3,i had zero emails that were classified,7,4.571428571428571,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,5.0,0.0,"('zero', 'CARDINAL')",1,2.0
2,the earth just started spinning faster than ever before and scientists are gravely concerned,14,5.642857142857143,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.3612,,0,2.0
2,sarasota  florida  teachers told they cannot purchase books  accept donated reading materials  order from scholastic or hold book fairs,19,5.947368421052632,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.2924,"('sarasota', 'GPE'), ('florida', 'GPE')",2,2.0
5,my treasury department is planning to pay down the national debt this quarter  which never happened under my predecessor,19,5.315789473684211,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.2732,"('treasury', 'ORG'), ('this quarter', 'DATE')",2,2.0
2,just in  the vatican has invited chelsea clinton  dr  fauci  new age figure deepak chopra and the ceos of moderna and pfizer to speak at a may conference focusing on  health  and the  soul,34,4.352941176470588,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,0.0,"('vatican', 'ORG'), ('clinton', 'PERSON'), ('dr  fauci', 'PERSON')",3,2.0
2,amy coney barrett overturned a     m verdict after a prison guard repeatedly raped a    year old inmate who was   months pregnant,21,4.761904761904762,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,-0.8074,"('coney barrett', 'PERSON'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('months', 'DATE')",3,2.0
2,photo shows a home depot worksheet on  privilege  used to train its employees,13,4.846153846153846,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.3612,,0,2.0
2,wladimir klitschko has auctioned off his      atlanta olympic games gold medal to raise money for the children of ukraine,19,5.157894736842105,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.4767,"('wladimir klitschko', 'PERSON'), ('atlanta', 'GPE')",2,2.0
5,our economy created over     million new jobs just last year  more jobs in one year than ever before in the history of the united states of america,27,4.296296296296297,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,0.5859,"('just last year', 'DATE'), ('one year', 'DATE'), ('the united states of america', 'GPE')",3,2.0
2,a molecule found in a himalayan fungus  kills cancer cells with    times potency,13,4.923076923076923,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.836,,0,2.0
2,binding masks to your face with gauze and wrapping pantyhose around your face and mask are now  suggestions to make your mask more  effective,24,4.833333333333333,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.5256,,0,2.0
6,joe biden holds the all time record for the most money received from pharma while in congress,17,4.529411764705882,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('joe biden', 'PERSON'), ('congress', 'ORG')",2,2.0
2,india has nearly     billion citizens  nearly     million of them live in extreme poverty   less than       per day  yet every singly  sic  indian citizen is required to have a valid form of id to vote in national elections,37,4.513513513513513,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,-0.5106,"('india', 'GPE'), ('nearly     million', 'CARDINAL'), ('indian', 'NORP')",3,2.0
5,in the      election  president trump voted from behind the desk in the white house in florida,16,4.5625,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('the white house', 'ORG'), ('florida', 'GPE')",2,2.0
2,most americans on minimum wage earn less than a dickensian allegory for destitution,13,5.461538461538462,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('americans', 'NORP')",1,2.0
6,says a new apple update will  scan u s iphones for images,12,3.75,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0,2.0
2,washington public school forces unvaccinated teens to wear ankle monitors  as a condition of playing team sports,17,5.588235294117647,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.2023,"('washington', 'GPE')",1,2.0
4,twitter has suspended the account of afghanistan s elected president  and have allowed the taliban to keep their accounts,19,5.368421052631579,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.4767,"('afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('taliban', 'ORG')",2,2.0
2,the u s  is  now importing         barrels of oil from russia   but that could have been prevented if the keystone xl pipeline hadn t been cancelled,26,4.269230769230769,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.3291,"('russia', 'GPE')",1,2.0
5,we had already issued several thousand special immigrant visas    to the  afghan  translators  when i came into office,18,5.277777777777778,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.4019,"('several thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('afghan', 'NORP')",2,2.0
4,mayo clinic study shows pfizer vaccine dropped to     effective,9,5.666666666666667,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.4767,"('mayo clinic study', 'ORG')",1,2.0
5,you re not going to get covid if you have these vaccinations,12,4.083333333333333,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,,0,2.0
5,we have now created over   million jobs since i took office  more jobs than have ever been created in the first five months of any presidency in modern history,29,4.413793103448276,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.4588,"('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('the first five months', 'DATE')",2,2.0
2,kids in cages  in border facilities are  at      capacity,9,4.666666666666667,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,,0,2.0
2,colorado  requires photo id to vote in person  requires signature verification for mail in ballots  which georgia got rid of  and prevents campaign workers from giving food  water to voters within     feet if they re wearing campaign apparel,38,5.131578947368421,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,26.0,0.4019,"('colorado', 'GPE'), ('georgia', 'GPE')",2,2.0
1,says deborah birx  traveled a great distance to see her family for thanksgiving  only to have them call the police and turn her in  she then     resigned,27,4.444444444444445,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.4767,"('deborah birx', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,minority farmers get big bonus  white ones get none   because of democrats,12,5.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.5423,"('democrats', 'NORP')",1,2.0
6,last week  the colorado supreme court declared that boulder s ar    ban was unconstitutional  today  there was a mass shooting in boulder,22,5.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.0,"('last week', 'DATE'), ('the colorado supreme court', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE')",3,2.0
5,the vast majority of the american people  support biden s      trillion rescue plan   including a majority of republicans,18,5.333333333333333,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.7184,"('american', 'NORP'), ('republicans', 'NORP')",2,2.0
6,a texas energy company billed a customer more than,9,4.666666666666667,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.2732,"('texas', 'GPE')",1,2.0
5,if you re making less than     an hour  you re living below the poverty wage,15,3.8,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.5106,,0,2.0
2,says a video shows joe biden boasted in       about voting for      miles of fence   and  talking about immigration in some entirely different ways than he does today,27,4.666666666666667,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.0,"('joe biden', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE')",2,2.0
2,go to antifa com and it takes you to biden s white house    just a slap in the face,19,3.263157894736842,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.1531,"('biden s white house', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,by revoking the keystone pipeline permit  biden is destroying        jobs,10,5.6,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.5574,,0,2.0
6,dems pass bill to vaccinate children without parental knowledge  consent,10,6.2,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.1695,"('dems', 'NORP')",1,2.0
5,tens and tens of thousands of bridges are in disrepair  some on the verge of collapse,16,4.3125,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.4939,"('tens and tens of thousands', 'CARDINAL')",1,2.0
2,the covid    pandemic has caused four of the eight  deadliest days in american history,14,4.928571428571429,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,"('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('days', 'DATE'), ('american', 'NORP')",4,2.0
5,people have lost faith in the ability of the vaccine to work  already  the numbers are really staggeringly low,19,4.7368421052631575,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.1082,,0,2.0
4,kyle rittenhouse used his covid    stimulus check to purchase the ar    he used in the fatal kenosha shooting,18,4.777777777777778,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,-0.5423,"('kyle', 'PERSON'), ('kenosha', 'GPE')",2,2.0
1,nobody s ever seen a number like this          economic growth is four times greater than what the experts expected,19,4.631578947368421,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.7845,"('four', 'CARDINAL')",1,2.0
5,says president donald trump  thinks that     an hour minimum wage is too much for essential workers,16,4.9375,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('donald trump', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,world renowned experts  declare that we should  live normally  practice simple hygiene   stay home when sick and use protective measures only with  the most vulnerable populations,26,5.6923076923076925,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.6697,,0,2.0
5,says donald trump  is pushing to slash medicare benefits,9,5.222222222222222,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.128,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('medicare', 'ORG')",2,2.0
2,says  joe   jill biden s income went from          in       to             in            anyone else want to know where that money is coming from,22,3.772727272727273,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0772,"('joe', 'PERSON'), ('jill biden s', 'PERSON')",2,2.0
4,days left to vote but if you are voting by mail  you need to vote today  usps says it needs a    day roundtrip to be counted on election day,29,3.689655172413793,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.0,"('today', 'DATE'), ('election day', 'DATE')",2,2.0
2,says joe biden told a factory worker   i don t work for you   while pointing a finger in the worker s face,22,3.6818181818181817,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.0,"('joe biden', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,says amy coney barrett said  calling a black employee the n word does not make for a hostile work environment,20,4.45,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,19.0,0.2924,"('coney barrett', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
4,president trump s net gain while in office     nancy pelosi s net gain while in office      million,17,4.352941176470588,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.7783,"('trump s', 'PERSON'), ('nancy pelosi s', 'PERSON')",2,2.0
2,japan has banned all  black lives matter  apparel from the olympics  no one can kneel or raise fists during the anthems either,22,4.636363636363637,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.6249,"('japan', 'GPE')",1,2.0
2,lumber  gas  wheat  coal and corn cost more in april       in joe biden s america  than they did a year earlier,21,3.857142857142857,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('joe biden s america', 'PERSON'), ('a year earlier', 'DATE')",2,2.0
4,a video shows  dems caught not wearing masks  at the white house,12,4.25,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('the white house', 'ORG')",1,2.0
4,after california taxes  trey lance s      m rookie deal becomes just    m,12,4.416666666666667,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('california', 'GPE')",1,2.0
2,montana is canceling unemployment because of a workforce shortage,9,6.333333333333333,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,-0.5994,"('montana', 'GPE')",1,2.0
6,million people watched biden s first presidential address to congress while far larger audiences watched donald trump s speeches,19,5.789473684210527,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.0,"('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('congress', 'ORG'), ('donald trump s', 'PERSON')",4,2.0
5,says his administration s efforts have led to more school reopenings,11,5.2727272727272725,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,,0,2.0
1,under operation warp speed  we ve pioneered groundbreaking therapies  reducing the fatality rate     since april,15,6.133333333333334,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.6705,"('april', 'DATE')",1,2.0
5,when i was vice president  violent crime fell     in this country      the murder rate now is up     across the nation this year under donald trump,25,4.36,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.9201,"('this year', 'DATE'), ('donald trump', 'PERSON')",2,2.0
2,if you go to antifa com  it takes you directly to joe biden s webpage   what s that tell ya try it yourself,23,3.565217391304348,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('joe biden s', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,two mail in ballots in pa  were  sent to the same person with their names on both a week and a half apart,23,3.5217391304347827,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,"('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('a week and a half', 'DATE')",2,2.0
2,says jacob blake  shot by police in kenosha  had a warrant for sexual assault and prior convictions for gun use,20,4.5,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.7351,"('jacob blake', 'PERSON'), ('kenosha', 'GPE')",2,2.0
6,this usps employee was caught taking down trump signs  these people are also responsible for the mail in ballots they are pushing so hard,24,4.708333333333333,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.1113,,0,2.0
2,says condoleezza rice said   if you are taught bitterness and anger  then you will believe you are a victim  you will feel aggrieved and the twin brother of aggrievement is entitlement  so now you think you are owed something and you don t have to work for it and now you re on a really bad road to nowhere because there are people who will play to that sense of victimhood  aggrievement and entitlement  and you still won t have a job,82,4.2317073170731705,52.0,52.0,52.0,52.0,52.0,-0.8479,"('condoleezza rice', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
1,for the past three years  the state senator who represents speaker nancy pelosi s san francisco  has led a push to abolish single family zoning in california,27,4.777777777777778,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,22.0,0.0,"('the past three years', 'DATE'), ('nancy pelosi', 'PERSON'), ('san francisco', 'GPE'), ('california', 'GPE')",4,2.0
2,trump s plan  would suspend the       your employer matches  see  you will not get that  nor will your wage or salary increase by,23,4.217391304347826,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.0,"('trump s plan', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,killing the payroll tax means killing social security,8,5.75,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.8126,,0,2.0
2,social media posts claim the u s  postal service  says you should give mail in ballots at least    days roundtrip  so  if you plan to vote by mail  election day isn t november    it s october   th,37,3.972972972972973,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,27.0,0.0,"('at least    days', 'DATE'), ('election day', 'DATE'), ('november', 'DATE'), ('october', 'DATE')",4,2.0
2,tea is allowing online learning with attendance stipulations but will not fund school districts if they do not open their schools   if schools do not open and are not funded there will be no more teachers or school at all,40,4.5,28.0,28.0,28.0,28.0,28.0,-0.4215,,0,2.0
2,two stamps needed for mail in ballots,7,4.428571428571429,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,4.0,0.0,"('two', 'CARDINAL')",1,2.0
2,businesses that refuse any legal tender can be fined and sued,11,4.636363636363637,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.1779,,0,2.0
2,lists eight wealthy politicians and public figures who  got millions  or close to it  in ppp loans,17,4.647058823529412,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.3612,"('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')",2,2.0
2,black lives matter demonstrators attack  elderly man wearing oxygen,9,6.444444444444445,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.4588,,0,2.0
6,lawyer couple who pointed guns at protesters are black lives matter backers  democrats and represent a police brutality victim,19,5.631578947368421,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,-0.7845,"('democrats', 'NORP')",1,2.0
6,nfl player  stood alone  while his whole team stayed in the locker room during the national anthem   a real american patriot,21,4.761904761904762,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,17.0,-0.25,"('nfl', 'ORG'), ('american', 'NORP')",2,2.0
2,says maine gov  janet mills is  using taxpayer money to buy cars for those on welfare  without a public hearing on the rules  if someone on welfare sells the car for cash without the state s approval  the rules don t allow the state to prosecute them for car theft,50,4.2,38.0,38.0,38.0,38.0,38.0,-0.5194,"('maine', 'GPE'), ('janet mills', 'PERSON')",2,2.0
6,biden said integrating black students would turn schools into  a jungle  a racial jungle,14,5.214285714285714,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('biden', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,trump administration just fired    scientists   cut off    grants at fauci s nih for not disclosing their ties to communist china,20,5.1,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,-0.5859,"('communist', 'NORP'), ('china', 'GPE')",2,2.0
6,cops in norway  require   years of training    people killed since       cops in finland  require   years of training    people killed since       cops in iceland  require   years of training    person killed since ever  cops in the u s   require    weeks of training         people killed since,43,4.8604651162790695,31.0,31.0,31.0,31.0,31.0,-0.9638,"('norway', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('finland', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('years', 'DATE')",5,2.0
2,the world health organization  now admits that asymptomatic transmission of covid    is very rare,14,5.714285714285714,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.296,"('the world health organization  now', 'ORG')",1,2.0
1,cases  numbers and deaths  of covid     are going down all over the country,13,4.384615384615385,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,,0,2.0
5,the u s  had    cdc staffers  in china to observe what was going on   president trump  brought home the vast majority of them  i think left only four in place,30,4.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,0.0,"('china', 'GPE'), ('only four', 'CARDINAL')",2,2.0
1,speaking about border apprehensions  said  we have some of the best numbers we ve ever had  southern border  the best numbers we ve ever had,25,4.48,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.8176,,0,2.0
2,bill gates worked to end livestock production  and is pushing lab grown meat,13,4.846153846153846,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('bill', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
1,you have areas of pennsylvania that are barely affected and  the governor wants  to keep them closed,17,4.823529411764706,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.079,"('pennsylvania', 'GPE')",1,2.0
2,joe biden said   the things i did while in elected office should not be made public while i am seeking a higher public office,24,4.166666666666667,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.0,"('joe biden', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
6,an appellate court found kamala harris and police  took part in framing and prosecuting a man  for a murder he didn t commit  paying a key witness         in relocation benefits for testifying against him,34,4.705882352941177,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,25.0,-0.2263,"('kamala harris', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
6,the leader of proud boys is the florida state director of latinos for trump,14,4.428571428571429,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.4767,"('florida', 'GPE')",1,2.0
2,says joe biden  wants american farmers to put their farmland into gvt  land banks   gvt would then tell farmers what  sustainable  plants they could grow,25,4.92,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.0,"('joe biden  ', 'PERSON'), ('american', 'NORP')",2,2.0
6,gas prices during the obama biden administration were       a gallon,10,5.3,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('the obama biden administration', 'ORG'), ('gallon', 'CARDINAL')",2,2.0
5,says president donald trump started a trade war that  led to a surge in farm bankruptcies,16,4.5625,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.5994,"('donald trump', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
4,says joe biden  disrespects servicemen  in telling them to  clap for that you stupid bastards,15,5.066666666666666,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.8126,"('joe biden  ', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,a graphic on u s  abortion rates shows larger declines during recent democratic presidential administrations  and says its due to the party s approach of making abortions unnecessary  rather than the republican party s approach of making the procedure illegal,40,5.425,32.0,32.0,32.0,32.0,32.0,0.2023,"('the republican party', 'ORG')",1,2.0
5,says donald trump is  the worst jobs president in recorded history,11,5.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,-0.6249,"('donald trump', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
4,quotes sen  mitt romney as saying   the merrick garland decision wasn t unfair   the notion that someone has to pay the price to make up for it is wrong,29,4.103448275862069,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,-0.765,"('quotes sen  mitt romney', 'ORG')",1,2.0
5,of every     kids in school today speak spanish,8,4.5,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,"('today', 'DATE'), ('spanish', 'NORP')",2,2.0
2,this is what kamala harris thinks about young americans    they are stupid,12,5.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.5267,"('kamala harris', 'PERSON'), ('americans', 'NORP')",2,2.0
2,in       joe biden voted in favor of taxing     of social security  and in       biden  was the deciding vote in raising the percentage taxed on social security from     to,28,4.392857142857143,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,18.0,0.7579,"('joe biden', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
5,says donald trump  let federal contractors double offshoring jobs in his first    months in office,15,5.333333333333333,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,0.0,"('donald trump', 'PERSON'), ('his first    months', 'DATE')",2,2.0
5,in every other major industrial country in the world   inflation is higher,12,5.083333333333333,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,10.0,0.0,,0,2.0
2,u s  orders millions of smallpox vaccines amid global monkeypox outbreak,11,5.545454545454546,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.0,"('millions', 'CARDINAL')",1,2.0
2,studies show plastics can help combat climate change,8,5.625,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0772,,0,2.0
6,indiana woman charged for mail in voter fraud  delivered     ballots with democrat box pre checked,15,5.266666666666667,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.6808,"('indiana', 'GPE'), ('democrat', 'NORP')",2,2.0
2,due to the baby formula shortage tricare will now pay to have it shipped directly to you,17,4.235294117647059,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,-0.34,,0,2.0
2,a chart shows china and india are leading in per capita carbon dioxide emissions,14,4.785714285714286,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('china', 'GPE'), ('india', 'GPE')",2,2.0
0,spike protein goes to nucleus and impairs dna repair,9,4.888888888888889,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,,0,2.0
6,timothy simpkins  a black teen shooter  got   day in jail and         bail  while kyle rittenhouse  a white teen  got   months in jail and    million bail   i think it s pretty evident     that white privilege is a myth,37,4.243243243243243,29.0,29.0,29.0,29.0,29.0,0.6908,"('timothy simpkins', 'PERSON'), ('kyle', 'PERSON'), ('months', 'DATE')",3,2.0
2,atheists are prohibited from holding office in   states,8,5.75,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,6.0,0.0,,0,2.0
6,photos show manila bay before and during rodrigo duterte s administration,11,5.727272727272728,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,0.0,"('show manila bay', 'LOC')",1,2.0
5,we ve created more jobs in the first eight months of my administration than any president in american history   total number of jobs created,24,4.791666666666667,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,16.0,0.5106,"('the first eight months', 'DATE'), ('american', 'NORP')",2,2.0
5,people who are vaccinated for the coronavirus  cannot spread it to you,12,4.833333333333333,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,,0,2.0
6,roe was the end of women dying from abortions,9,4.111111111111111,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,,0,2.0
5,raising the debt limit is usually a bipartisan undertaking,9,5.555555555555555,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,-0.3612,,0,2.0
2,there have been     criminal indictments under three recent republican presidents and only three indictments under three recent democratic presidents,19,6.684210526315789,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,-0.5267,"('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('republican', 'NORP'), ('only three', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('democratic', 'NORP')",5,2.0
2,elaine chao busted sending     million contract to help mitch mcconnell win reelection,12,5.916666666666667,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,9.0,0.7579,"('elaine chao', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
2,says nike pays factory workers      of whom are women      cents an hour  and has them work     to    hours a week,20,3.85,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,,0,2.0
2,people with pre existing mental health conditions have access to firearms and not health care,15,5.266666666666667,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,12.0,-0.3875,,0,2.0
6,says ann landers said   at age     we worry about what others think of us  at age     we don t care what they think  at age     we discover that they have not been thinking of us at all,37,3.5945945945945947,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,0.0772,"('ann landers', 'PERSON')",1,2.0
1,for the first time in history  most new hires of prime working age are minorities and women,17,4.352941176470588,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,13.0,0.0,"('first', 'ORDINAL')",1,2.0
1,of the world s population lives in countries where religious liberty is in significant danger or even completely outlawed,19,5.421052631578948,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,14.0,0.2023,,0,2.0
0,says elizabeth warren  was paid          to teach one class,9,4.555555555555555,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.0,"('elizabeth warren', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')",2,2.0
5,the obama biden administration did not conduct workplace raids in fact  it ended them,14,5.071428571428571,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,11.0,0.0,"('the obama biden administration', 'ORG')",1,2.0
1,the united states is  very energy independent,7,5.428571428571429,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,7.0,0.6361,"('the united states', 'GPE')",1,2.0
1,the homicide rate in baltimore is significantly higher than el salvador  honduras  guatemala       i believe it s higher than afghanistan,20,5.5,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,15.0,0.0,"('baltimore', 'GPE'), ('el salvador', 'GPE'), ('guatemala       ', 'PERSON'), ('afghanistan', 'GPE')",4,2.0
1,i ve had tremendous republican support  i have a           approval rating  as of this morning  in the republican party  that s an all time record,25,4.32,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,21.0,0.8176,"('republican', 'NORP'), ('the republican party', 'ORG')",2,2.0
5,the      crime bill  did not generate mass incarceration,8,5.375,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,8.0,-0.5423,,0,2.0
2,quotes mark twain as saying of journalists that it is  far better  to  fear the media for they will steal your honor  and describes them as  a horde of ignorant  self complacent simpletons,33,4.545454545454546,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,20.0,-0.4019,,0,2.0
